<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Biden on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/biden/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Biden on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2024 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 19:21:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/biden/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Middle East Crisis Biden Outlines Cease-fire Proposal to End War in Gaza</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-05-31-middle-east-crisis-biden-outlines-cease-fire-proposal-to-end-war-in-gaza/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 May 2024 19:21:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-05-31-middle-east-crisis-biden-outlines-cease-fire-proposal-to-end-war-in-gaza/</guid>
      <description>President Joe Biden on Thursday outlined a cease-fire proposal to end the war in Gaza, saying he spoke with Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu and Palestinian Authority President Mahmoud Abbas about the plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Musk accuses Biden of lying about the immigration crisis</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-03-03-musk-accuses-biden-of-lying-about-the-immigration-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-03-03-musk-accuses-biden-of-lying-about-the-immigration-crisis/</guid>
      <description>The billionaire and American businessman, Elon Musk, accused the American president on Sunday of lying about the immigration crisis, stating that President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s remarks about wanting to solve the issue of illegal immigration are &amp;ldquo;pure lies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Joe Biden, nominee-in-waiting. And waiting. And waiting.</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/joe-biden-nominee-in-waiting-and-waiting-and-waiting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 03:16:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/joe-biden-nominee-in-waiting-and-waiting-and-waiting/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;mdash; In the three weeks since his blowout win in the South Carolina primary, Joe Biden has emerged as the Democratic presidential nominee-in-waiting. But, amid the uncertainty of the coronavirus pandemic, put the emphasis on waiting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biden wins endorsement from NEA, nation&#39;s largest union</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/biden-wins-endorsement-from-nea-nations-largest-union/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Mar 2020 05:17:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/biden-wins-endorsement-from-nea-nations-largest-union/</guid>
      <description>The nation&amp;rsquo;s largest labor union has lined up behind Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s presidential campaign, with the National Education Association on Saturday endorsing the former vice president for the Democratic nomination over his last remaining primary rival Bernie Sanders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Latest: Biden faces down pro-gun worker at Detroit plant</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-latest-biden-faces-down-pro-gun-worker-at-detroit-plant/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 17:18:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-latest-biden-faces-down-pro-gun-worker-at-detroit-plant/</guid>
      <description>DETROIT (AP) &amp;mdash; The Latest on the 2020 Democratic presidential primaries (all times local):
11:35 a.m.
Joe Biden has faced down a pro-gun worker in a testy exchange over his plan to reinstate the assault weapons ban.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biden wins 8 Super Tuesday states; Sanders takes California</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/biden-wins-8-super-tuesday-states-sanders-takes-california/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 07:20:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/biden-wins-8-super-tuesday-states-sanders-takes-california/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;mdash; A resurgent Joe Biden scored victories from Texas to Massachusetts on Huge Tuesday, revitalizing a presidential inform that used to be teetering on the threshold of catastrophe correct days earlier.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Biden fights for momentum in Democrats&#39; shifting primary</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/biden-fights-for-momentum-in-democrats-shifting-primary/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 08:21:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/biden-fights-for-momentum-in-democrats-shifting-primary/</guid>
      <description>SELMA, Ala. (AP) &amp;mdash; An emboldened Joe Biden is attempting to solid himself as the decided reasonable different to revolutionary Bernie Sanders as the Democrats&#39; fearful presidential field raced in direction of Neat Tuesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Scandal of Ukraine&#34; .. Suspicions about the complicity of Pompeo and Pines</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/suspicions-about-the-complicity-of-pompeo-and-pines/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 10:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/suspicions-about-the-complicity-of-pompeo-and-pines/</guid>
      <description>As public hearings into the investigation into the ouster of US President Donald Trump enter their second week, there is suspicion of complicity over US Vice President Mike Pence and Secretary of State Mike Pompeo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The White House Refuses to Cooperate with Investigations The move would put the United States in a constitutional crisis</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-white-house-refuses-to-cooperate-with-investigations-the-move-would-put-the-united-states-in-a-constitutional-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 11:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-white-house-refuses-to-cooperate-with-investigations-the-move-would-put-the-united-states-in-a-constitutional-crisis/</guid>
      <description>The White House has decided to refuse to cooperate with ongoing investigations that Democrats are seeking to begin proceedings to isolate President Donald Trump, arguing that the investigation lacks &amp;ldquo;constitutional legitimacy&amp;rdquo; and would put the United States in a constitutional crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
