<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Syria on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/syria/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Syria on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2024 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 13:07:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/syria/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Times: Changing Alliances Feed Syria War</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/times-changing-alliances-feed-syria-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 13:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/times-changing-alliances-feed-syria-war/</guid>
      <description>An analysis by the Middle East Times correspondent Richard Spinner says the changing alliances that fuel the war that has ravaged Syria for years are endless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After targeting sites in Syria, Israel is preparing for an Iranian strike</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-is-preparing-for-an-iranian-strike/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 10:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-is-preparing-for-an-iranian-strike/</guid>
      <description>JERUSALEM (Reuters) &amp;ndash; Tel Aviv is preparing for a possible missile strike by Iranian forces in Syria in the coming hours or days in response to a dawn attack on its positions near Damascus that it said belonged to the Iranian Qods Force, Israeli security sources said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ankara warns of a new operation in Syria if Washington and Moscow fail to honor their commitments</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/ankara-warns-of-a-new-operation-in-syria-if-washington-and-moscow-fail-to-honor-their-commitments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 07:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/ankara-warns-of-a-new-operation-in-syria-if-washington-and-moscow-fail-to-honor-their-commitments/</guid>
      <description>Turkish Foreign Minister Mevlut Cavusoglu said that the United States and Russia did not do what is necessary under the agreements on northern Syria, stressing the need to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia sends 300 additional troops to the Syrian-Turkish border</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/russia-sends-300-additional-troops-to-the-syrian-turkish-border/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 21:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/russia-sends-300-additional-troops-to-the-syrian-turkish-border/</guid>
      <description>The Russian Defense Ministry announced the arrival of about 300 Russian military police to Syria to help the withdrawal of Kurdish forces from the border with Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Israel and Iran: dangerous vortex and deterrence</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-and-iran-dangerous-vortex-and-deterrence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-and-iran-dangerous-vortex-and-deterrence/</guid>
      <description>In the face of Hezbollah, which is building a new front, and the Iranian threat, whose nature is changing from time to time, the Israeli army is building a concrete wall and advanced observation posts near the northern border, in a constant battle between parade and deterrence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Turkish Defense Ministry announced that its forces took control of the M4 highway with a depth of 30 to 35 kilometers inside Syrian territory</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-turkish-defense-ministry-announced-that-its-forces-took-control-of-the-m4-highway/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Oct 2019 16:38:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-turkish-defense-ministry-announced-that-its-forces-took-control-of-the-m4-highway/</guid>
      <description>The Turkish Defense Ministry announced that its forces took control of the M4 highway with a depth of 30 to 35 kilometers inside Syrian territory, following its takeover of the city of Tall Abyad in northeastern Syria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s policy in Syria could reorganize the state</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trumps-policy-in-syria-could-reorganize-the-state/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 12:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trumps-policy-in-syria-could-reorganize-the-state/</guid>
      <description>US President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;reactionary&amp;rdquo; foreign policy would bring the Islamic State back to Syria, writer Kim Seggupta says.
One of the hallmarks of Trump&amp;rsquo;s foreign policy is his lack of success against adversaries and his failure to stand by allies, the writer adds in an article in The Independent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continued international reactions to the Turkish military operation in Syria</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/continued-international-reactions-to-the-turkish-military-operation-in-syria/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 18:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/continued-international-reactions-to-the-turkish-military-operation-in-syria/</guid>
      <description>International reactions to Turkey&amp;rsquo;s launch on Wednesday of a large-scale military operation in northeast Syria to develop a safe zone evolved. France and the Netherlands summoned their ambassadors to protest against the military attack, while Iran called on Turkey to immediately halt the military operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns and Kurds mobilize .. List of the latest developments of the Turkish operation in Syria</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/russia-warns-and-kurds-mobilize-list-of-the-latest-developments-of-the-turkish-operation-in-syria/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 12:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/russia-warns-and-kurds-mobilize-list-of-the-latest-developments-of-the-turkish-operation-in-syria/</guid>
      <description>Turkish troops are preparing to launch a military operation in northern Syria with the aim of keeping Kurdish fighters out of their borders and establishing a safe area, enabling Syrian refugees to return home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Kurds and the Syria Crisis From the Equation to the Board</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-kurds-and-the-syria-crisis-from-the-equation-to-the-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-kurds-and-the-syria-crisis-from-the-equation-to-the-board/</guid>
      <description>Much water has flowed since the return of Kurdish Democratic Union leader Saleh Muslim Mohammad to the northern Syrian city of Qamishli in April 2011, coming from the PKK strongholds in the Qandil mountains of northern Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert: Washington does not want to face NATO ally &#34;Turkey&#34;</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/expert-washington-does-not-want-to-face-nato-ally-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 13:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/expert-washington-does-not-want-to-face-nato-ally-turkey/</guid>
      <description>Political analyst and adviser Ali Hussein Bakir, the US administration concluded that it would be &amp;ldquo;absurd&amp;rdquo; to engage in a confrontation with Turkey after President Donald Trump confirmed his commitment to withdraw troops from Syria.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
