<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>China on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/china/</link>
    <description>Recent content in China on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2024 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 03:19:22 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/china/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Hardest-hit China, South Korea count 767 unusual virus conditions</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/hardest-hit-china-south-korea-count-767-unusual-virus-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 03:19:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/hardest-hit-china-south-korea-count-767-unusual-virus-conditions/</guid>
      <description>BEIJING (AP) &amp;mdash; South Korea and China each and every reported hundreds more virus conditions Thursday as the unusual illness persists in the worst-hit areas and spreads past borders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump In India And What He&#39;s Doing That The MSM Isn&#39;t Telling You</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-in-india-and-what-hes-doing-that-the-msm-isnt-telling-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 14:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-in-india-and-what-hes-doing-that-the-msm-isnt-telling-you/</guid>
      <description>Namaste, that actually means hi in Indiana, don’t worry I’m not turning a full hippie-dippie, but anyway, Donald Trump officially retweeted upon the announcement of his visit to India which we will be breaking down the significance of geopolitically, especially with all the incredible news happening around American foreign policy including the latest information about the Afghanistan Taliban peace deal that you’re not hearing about in the mainstream media, the extremely messy situation unfolding right now in Syria with Turkey Russia and China is very involved in what looks like a situation that will soon escalate to very dangerous proportions, and then, of course, we’re also gonna be talking about China Philippines there is, of course, a lot more all specifically surrounding American hegemony foreign policy, geopolitical updates that of course, you won’t hear from MSM, so I mean you don’t even hear about the topic of foreign policy being discussed in the presidential debates but it is a key important factor since American foreign policy is essentially policy of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China 2020 Valentine&#39;s Day a how to</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/china-2020-valentines-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 15:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/china-2020-valentines-day/</guid>
      <description>Valentine’s Day in 2020 and the epidemic is not over yet. Two people cannot meet to eat, watch movies, as before. Many lovers ca n&amp;rsquo;t even meet at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is there no specific medicine against Coronavirus in the world so far?</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/medicine-against-coronavirus-in-the-world-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 14:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/medicine-against-coronavirus-in-the-world-so-far/</guid>
      <description>The severe acute respiratory syndrome (SARS) that broke out in Guangdong in February 2003 and the Middle East respiratory syndrome (MERS) that broke out in Saudi Arabia in September 2012 were caused by SARS-CoV and MERS-CoV coronaviruses, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Huge crowd of protesters in Hong Kong for six months of protest</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/huge-crowd-of-protesters-in-hong-kong-for-six-months-of-protest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Dec 2019 18:19:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/huge-crowd-of-protesters-in-hong-kong-for-six-months-of-protest/</guid>
      <description>The rally took place two weeks after the victory of the pro-democracy opposition in the local elections. 800,000 people were reunited, according to pro-democracy activists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China threatens US retaliation for supporting Hong Kong protests</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/china-threatens-us-retaliation-for-supporting-hong-kong-protests/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 10:54:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/china-threatens-us-retaliation-for-supporting-hong-kong-protests/</guid>
      <description>BEIJING (Reuters) &amp;ndash; China&amp;rsquo;s Foreign Ministry on Tuesday summoned a senior US diplomat and threatened retaliatory measures against Washington after the US Senate adopted a law supporting demonstrators in Hong Kong, which has been under protests since June.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beijing&#39;s weapons in battle and Why America waged a trade war on China</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/beijings-weapons-in-battle-and-why-america-waged-a-trade-war-on-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 20:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/beijings-weapons-in-battle-and-why-america-waged-a-trade-war-on-china/</guid>
      <description>In the aftermath of the Cold War, the United States changed its policy and priorities and viewed China&amp;rsquo;s economic emergence as a major threat to its interests in the decades to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After months of blacklisting .. Huawei launches superior technology for the fifth generation</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/after-months-of-blacklisting-huawei-launches-superior-technology-for-the-fifth-generation/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 12:24:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/after-months-of-blacklisting-huawei-launches-superior-technology-for-the-fifth-generation/</guid>
      <description>BEIJING (Reuters) &amp;ndash; China&amp;rsquo;s Huawei on Wednesday launched a new generation of mobile phone antennas for its 5G network and expects an acceleration in network upgrades led by the three operators in its huge Chinese market.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After China described him as a poison .. Apple acquiesces and removes a special application maps Hong Kong</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/after-china-described-him-as-a-poison-apple-acquiesces-and-removes-a-special-application-maps-hong-kong/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 12:28:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/after-china-described-him-as-a-poison-apple-acquiesces-and-removes-a-special-application-maps-hong-kong/</guid>
      <description>HONG KONG (Reuters) &amp;ndash; Apple on Wednesday removed an application from its shop that protesters in Hong Kong used to track police moves through, claiming it violated rules because it was used to ambush police.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
