<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>health on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in health on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2020 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 22:22:09 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Europeans sing health workers&#39; praises nightly from windows</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/europeans-sing-health-workers-praises-nightly-from-windows/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 22:22:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/europeans-sing-health-workers-praises-nightly-from-windows/</guid>
      <description>PARIS (AP) &amp;mdash; At a time of isolation, people in many European cities hit hard by the new coronavirus are taking at least a minute each night to come together in gratitude.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Health Department website was attacked in the middle of the coronavirus pandemic</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-health-department-website-was-attacked-in-the-middle-of-the-coronavirus-pandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 13:23:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-health-department-website-was-attacked-in-the-middle-of-the-coronavirus-pandemic/</guid>
      <description>The US Health and Human Services Department was the victim of a cyberattack yesterday, the agency confirmed to Recode.
Bloomberg, which was first to report the attack on Monday morning, initially described it as a hack, but updates to its story removed the word &amp;ldquo;hack,&amp;rdquo; instead referring to it as &amp;ldquo;multiple incidents of a cyber intrusion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ultimate joints pain guide from zero to finish</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-ultimate-joints-pain-guide-from-zero-to-finish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 21:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-ultimate-joints-pain-guide-from-zero-to-finish/</guid>
      <description>One of the most health issues that confront the 21th-century population is joint pain from knee pain to neck pain, ankle, hip or pelvic pain, especially for people who suffer from severe health problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>46 health myths most people believe in</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/46-health-myths-most-people-believe-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:47:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/46-health-myths-most-people-believe-in/</guid>
      <description>We all heard at some stage in our lives some advice from our parents, family or friends that we looked after to appear that it is totally false, maybe even the opposite of truth, people to transfer a lot of talk mouth to mouth without checking after it, we tried in this article to compile a list of the most common myths people believe in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nutrients that may change your health forever and for good</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/nutrients-that-may-change-your-health-forever-and-for-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 13:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/nutrients-that-may-change-your-health-forever-and-for-good/</guid>
      <description>So we all know that the food that we eat contains calories but looking into it more we could consider calories as energy, we can split the energy into free main types known as macronutrients these free are known as protein carbohydrates and fat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anorexia -- You will not believe how this eating disorder can transform people</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/anorexia-you-will-not-believe-how-this-eating-disorder-can-transform-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/anorexia-you-will-not-believe-how-this-eating-disorder-can-transform-people/</guid>
      <description>Patients with anorexia nervosa the most lethal psychiatric condition feel compelled to diet and exercise despite negative consequences restricting food become automatic and consuming high-calorie foods causes anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Signs That You May Be Suffering From Vitamin D Deficiency</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/7-signs-that-you-may-be-suffering-from-vitamin-d-deficiency/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 14:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/7-signs-that-you-may-be-suffering-from-vitamin-d-deficiency/</guid>
      <description>According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), 32 percent of adults and children in the U.S. are vitamin D deficient. While people get vitamin D from food and sunlight, Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>British Company Releases Pictures Of World&#39;s First ‘Smart Condoms&#39;</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/british-company-releases-pictures-of-worlds-first-smart-condoms/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 14:30:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/british-company-releases-pictures-of-worlds-first-smart-condoms/</guid>
      <description>These days, most people have some kind of smart device, whether it be a phone, a watch, or something that helps you track your daily steps.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Your Fingernails Say About Your Health</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-your-fingernails-say-about-your-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 08:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-your-fingernails-say-about-your-health/</guid>
      <description>Ever wonder why your nails are so brittle, yellow, or otherwise discolored? Though you may not know it, these seemingly harmless symptoms may indicate you have some underlying health issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Use Or Ingest Ginger If You Have Any of These Four Conditions</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/dont-use-or-ingest-ginger-if-you-have-any-of-these-four-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 08:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/dont-use-or-ingest-ginger-if-you-have-any-of-these-four-conditions/</guid>
      <description>Ginger is a highly nutritious plant. In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s widely used as a folk medicine for a number of conditions. That&amp;rsquo;s because its active components, including gingerol and shogaols, have a ton of health benefits to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Diet Doesn&#39;t Just Help With Weight Loss. It May Also Prevent Major Diseases.</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/this-diet-doesnt-just-help-with-weight-loss-it-may-also-prevent-major-diseases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 09:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/this-diet-doesnt-just-help-with-weight-loss-it-may-also-prevent-major-diseases/</guid>
      <description>If you have friends or family members who&amp;rsquo;ve lost weight or are very focused on their health, chances are you&amp;rsquo;ve heard of the ketogenic diet. As those who&amp;rsquo;ve adopted the low-carb, high-fat diet will tell you, it comes with many health benefits, especially when it comes to dropping extra pounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Alarming Symptoms Of Tonsilloliths That Should Never Be Ignored</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/6-alarming-symptoms-of-tonsilloliths-that-should-never-be-ignored/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 09:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/6-alarming-symptoms-of-tonsilloliths-that-should-never-be-ignored/</guid>
      <description>Ever experience a sore throat but think there could be more to it than having strep throat or tonsillitis? Maybe you&amp;rsquo;ve noticed your tonsils are swollen or you see something strange at the back of your throat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colon Cancer Survival Rate Is 92% When Caught Early -- Don&#39;t Ignore These 5 Early Warning Signs</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/colon-cancer-survival-rate-is-92-when-caught-early-dont-ignore-these-5-early-warning-signs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 08:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/colon-cancer-survival-rate-is-92-when-caught-early-dont-ignore-these-5-early-warning-signs/</guid>
      <description>Cancers have a way of striking when we least expect them to because they come with symptoms that are very similar to other symptoms that will be experienced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woman Wears Mascara To Bed For 25 Years And Never Washes Her Face -- See Under Her Eyelid</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/woman-wears-mascara-to-bed-for-25-years-and-never-washes-her-face-see-under-her-eyelid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 08:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/woman-wears-mascara-to-bed-for-25-years-and-never-washes-her-face-see-under-her-eyelid/</guid>
      <description>Most of us wear our makeup to bed on occasion. We may come in and just be too tired to wash it off so we just go to bed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
