<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>wellness on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/categories/wellness/</link>
    <description>Recent content in wellness on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2024 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 09:37:58 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/categories/wellness/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kind Thoughts Strategy: How to Become Tolerant of the Unknown</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/kind-thoughts-strategy-how-to-become-tolerant-of-the-unknown/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 09:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/kind-thoughts-strategy-how-to-become-tolerant-of-the-unknown/</guid>
      <description>In March, I asked on social networks what was the most difficult for people during the COVID-19 pandemic. I got more than 100 answers and found that in many ways people have the same problem: the unknown.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>DIY -- 24 method how to make your own hand sanitizer</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/diy-24-method-how-to-make-your-own-hand-sanitizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/diy-24-method-how-to-make-your-own-hand-sanitizer/</guid>
      <description>Liquid hand sanitizers-mostly alcohol-based gels-have experienced an explosion in popularity over the last 10 years. If you’ve recently traveled by plane or set foot in a classroom in the US, chances are you’ve seen hand sanitizers in use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t rush to deploy coronavirus vaccines and drugs</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/dont-rush-to-deploy-coronavirus-vaccines-and-drugs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 11:25:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/dont-rush-to-deploy-coronavirus-vaccines-and-drugs/</guid>
      <description>Around the world, I am seeing efforts to support ‘quick-fix&#39; programmes aimed at developing vaccines and therapeutics against COVID-19.
Groups in the United States and China are already planning to test vaccines in healthy human volunteers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are Gut Boosters  BS?</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/are-gut-boosters-bs/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 13:01:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/are-gut-boosters-bs/</guid>
      <description>Supplement companies claim that prebiotics (which are one thing) and probiotics (another thing!) can strengthen immunity, aid weight loss, and even extend life. MELISSA MATTHEWS fact-checks all that.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Medical mind-reading brain scanners to ask patients who cannot speak</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/medical-mind-reading-brain-scanners-to-ask-patients-who-cannot-speak/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 20:15:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/medical-mind-reading-brain-scanners-to-ask-patients-who-cannot-speak/</guid>
      <description>Doctors are using brain scanners to ask patients who cannot speak about their treatment wishes
When a person sustains a severe brain injury that leaves them unable to communicate, their families and doctors often have to make life-or-death decisions about their care for them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A harmful ingredient hidden in vegetable juices</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/a-harmful-ingredient-hidden-in-vegetable-juices/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 16:32:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/a-harmful-ingredient-hidden-in-vegetable-juices/</guid>
      <description>Vegetable juices are a great way to get nutrients without excessive calories, so they can substitute for a proportion of the actual vegetables, and without the effort of peeling, slicing or cooking.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The healthiest and easiest Mediterranean diet to follow</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-healthiest-and-easiest-mediterranean-diet-to-follow/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 21:06:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-healthiest-and-easiest-mediterranean-diet-to-follow/</guid>
      <description>Discover the benefits and keys of one of the most ideal diets for our health and figure. With weekly downloadable menu included.
Every day you get up with new diets, more blacklisted names of banned products and new superfoods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 types of tea to help you sleep</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/4-types-of-tea-to-help-you-sleep/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Feb 2020 16:43:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/4-types-of-tea-to-help-you-sleep/</guid>
      <description>To sleep better, we may need to drink some beneficial teas. In her report, published by the American “Basel” website, author Elizabeth Inks reviewed the types of tea that have relaxing properties, which help them sleep faster and for a longer period of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doctors in Thailand announce discovery of the deadly corona virus treatment</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/doctors-in-thailand-announce-discovery-of-the-deadly-corona-virus-treatment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 13:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/doctors-in-thailand-announce-discovery-of-the-deadly-corona-virus-treatment/</guid>
      <description>Doctors in Thailand said they had successfully treated one of the patients with the Coronavir virus with a combination of antiviral drugs, according to a briefing yesterday from the Ministry of Health reported by CNN.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>When does throat pain indicate a thyroid tumor</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/when-does-throat-pain-indicate-a-thyroid-tumor/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 18:48:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/when-does-throat-pain-indicate-a-thyroid-tumor/</guid>
      <description>The German Association of Otolaryngologists said that sore throat is not due to a common cold, especially if it is not accompanied by the distinct symptoms of a cold, which are runny nose, sneezing, and coughing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 foods you should deprive yourself of after the age of 30</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/7-foods-you-should-deprive-yourself-of-after-the-age-of-30/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 05:15:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/7-foods-you-should-deprive-yourself-of-after-the-age-of-30/</guid>
      <description>Once you reach the age of thirty, your body metabolic rate will decline, so you should be careful with foods you eat at this age, otherwise, you may be overweight, obese, and health problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are the causes of testicle pain</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-are-the-causes-of-testicle-pain/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 09:28:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-are-the-causes-of-testicle-pain/</guid>
      <description>Most men are concerned when they experience pain in the testicles, but not all pain is an indication of a serious illness. And there is no reason to worry if a man feels pain in the testicles during or after intercourse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five habits that lead to belly fat</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/five-habits-that-lead-to-belly-fat/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 09:16:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/five-habits-that-lead-to-belly-fat/</guid>
      <description>The German Nutrition Association reported that there are some wrong habits that lead to the accumulation of fat in the abdominal area, including:
1- Lack of sleep Lack of sleep causes the body to produce more steroid hormone cortisol, which is responsible for cravings to eat and to reduce the level of cortisol you should sleep for between seven and eight hours at night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intermittent fasting advantages and the right method for you</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/intermittent-fasting-advantages-and-the-right-method-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Dec 2019 07:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/intermittent-fasting-advantages-and-the-right-method-for-you/</guid>
      <description>Intermittent fasting or part-time fasting is not only the ideal introduction to ketosis, but it also has several advantages for your performance and performance. You can find out about the effects of skipping a meal every now and then and which method you can use to start intermittent fasting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The discovery leads to drugs targeting dozens of types of cancer</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-discovery-leads-to-drugs-targeting-dozens-of-types-of-cancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 12:00:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-discovery-leads-to-drugs-targeting-dozens-of-types-of-cancer/</guid>
      <description>By turning off genes one by one, researchers from the United Kingdom and the United States have targeted cancer with new drugs.
The author, Sean Lintern, said in a report in the British newspaper “The Independent”, that scientists have made an important step towards developing new drugs that target specific genes within dozens of types of cancer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A warning to vegetarians about their danger</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/a-warning-to-vegetarians-about-their-danger/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 17:33:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/a-warning-to-vegetarians-about-their-danger/</guid>
      <description>Vegetarians have advised vegetarians to take the risk of vitamin B12 deficiency seriously, otherwise, they may experience nerve damage, permanent (numbness) and spinal cord degeneration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Food that helps treat constipation</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/food-that-helps-treat-constipation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 06:39:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/food-that-helps-treat-constipation/</guid>
      <description>Studies have reported that the defecation rate of only three times or less during one week is a sign that the person suffers from constipation, according to the American Institute of Diabetes and Digestive and Kidney Diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 stimulant alternatives that keep you away from coffee</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/6-stimulant-alternatives-that-keep-you-away-from-coffee/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 24 Dec 2019 05:28:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/6-stimulant-alternatives-that-keep-you-away-from-coffee/</guid>
      <description>People often drink coffee when they feel lethargic or when they are drowsy and want to get rid of it. However, there are six food substitutes for coffee that give the body a lot of energy and energy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Processed foods threaten you with diabetes</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/processed-foods-threaten-you-with-diabetes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 04:26:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/processed-foods-threaten-you-with-diabetes/</guid>
      <description>A new study indicated that people who eat many processed foods are more likely to develop diabetes compared to those whose diets contain more foods in their natural form.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Scottish company claims to produce a miracle drug that treats diabetes and multiple sclerosis</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/a-scottish-company-claims-to-produce-a-miracle-drug-that-treats-diabetes-to-multiple-sclerosis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 12:55:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/a-scottish-company-claims-to-produce-a-miracle-drug-that-treats-diabetes-to-multiple-sclerosis/</guid>
      <description>A Scottish company claims to have a solution that can make fecal transplants more acceptable, by drying healthy bacteria in the feces and putting them in the grain, which opens the door to treatment for many diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 magic fruits that help you get rid of belly</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/6-magic-fruits-that-help-you-get-rid-of-belly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 19:17:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/6-magic-fruits-that-help-you-get-rid-of-belly/</guid>
      <description>The German Nutrition Association reported that there are types of fruits that contain important nutrients that help remove belly fat (rumen), which negatively affects the body, and increase the risk of diabetes, heart disease, and metabolism:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 weapons to fight viruses</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/4-weapons-to-fight-viruses/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 18:59:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/4-weapons-to-fight-viruses/</guid>
      <description>The German magazine &amp;ldquo;Freuden&amp;rdquo; provided some advice and instructions that can protect against viruses and strengthen the immune system to fight viruses in the body, namely:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These are the best natural antibiotics, including Echinacea</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/these-are-the-best-natural-antibiotics-including-echinacea/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 17:41:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/these-are-the-best-natural-antibiotics-including-echinacea/</guid>
      <description>There are different herbs that can act as natural antibiotics, as in addition to their role in fighting winter diseases, these herbs play an effective role against some skin diseases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The world is heading towards vegetarianism and these are its advantages and dangers</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-world-is-heading-towards-vegetarianism-and-these-are-its-advantages-and-dangers/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 10:26:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-world-is-heading-towards-vegetarianism-and-these-are-its-advantages-and-dangers/</guid>
      <description>(AZ) An Egyptian engineer, thirty, tall, with a sporty appearance, with a sarcastic smile mixed with confusion. He says, &amp;ldquo;After our marriage, the bride prepared a table full of barbecues, but she went crazy when she left making her hands looking for a boiled egg and a piece of cheese, so I wrote on Facebook.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Has Alzheimer&#39;s disease ended? Invented artificial neurons instead of lost brain cells</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/invented-artificial-neurons-instead-of-lost-brain-cells/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 16:53:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/invented-artificial-neurons-instead-of-lost-brain-cells/</guid>
      <description>Scientists have invented artificial neurons that can be implanted in the brain to repair damage from Alzheimer&amp;rsquo;s disease or other neurodegenerative conditions.
In a report published in the British Telegraph newspaper, writer Sarah Knapton said that the electronic cells developed by teams at the University of Bath and a team of international collaborators are placed on a silicon chip and mimic the responses of biological neurons when they are powered by the nervous system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t be fooled by the health aura Vegetable milk is more sugary than cow&#39;s milk</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/dont-be-fooled-by-the-health-aura-vegetable-milk-is-more-sugary-than-cows-milk/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 16:41:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/dont-be-fooled-by-the-health-aura-vegetable-milk-is-more-sugary-than-cows-milk/</guid>
      <description>Health experts warned that beverages containing a liquid milk substitute may be less healthy than beverages made from cow&amp;rsquo;s milk, advising shoppers to pay attention to the tricks that market the &amp;ldquo;healthy aura&amp;rdquo; of plant foods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Does hair coloring cause breast cancer? That&#39;s what you should know</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/does-hair-coloring-cause-breast-cancer/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 15:05:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/does-hair-coloring-cause-breast-cancer/</guid>
      <description>NEW YORK (Reuters Health) &amp;ndash; Breast cancer is 14 percent more likely to occur in women who have dyed their hair, according to a study by a British surgeon recently.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do you enjoy an iron memory or suffer from the scourge of forgetfulness?</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/do-you-enjoy-an-iron-memory-or-suffer-from-the-scourge-of-forgetfulness/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 13:53:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/do-you-enjoy-an-iron-memory-or-suffer-from-the-scourge-of-forgetfulness/</guid>
      <description>Turning the house upside down in search of car keys just two minutes before leaving the house is a classic. Sometimes you try to focus, remember and review every second you passed the day before, and you certainly tried to remember the name of the hero of the movie you are watching with your friend, but to no avail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn about fibromyalgia symptoms and methods of treatment</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/learn-about-fibromyalgia-symptoms-and-methods-of-treatment/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 15:50:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/learn-about-fibromyalgia-symptoms-and-methods-of-treatment/</guid>
      <description>Fibromyalgia, or fibromyalgia, is a chronic condition caused by an imbalance in the treatment of pain in the body, according to the Federal Health Awareness Center.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The main etiology of depression</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-main-etiology-of-depression/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 12:54:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-main-etiology-of-depression/</guid>
      <description>Depression is one of the most common and common mental disorders, and although it is widely known, its causes are rare.
Depression is an emotional disorder in which emotional pain and discomfort are expressed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A new benefit for virgin olive oil</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/a-new-benefit-for-virgin-olive-oil/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Nov 2019 11:09:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/a-new-benefit-for-virgin-olive-oil/</guid>
      <description>Adding extra virgin olive oil to your daily diet protects against mental aging associated with aging, leading to a type of dementia called frontotemporal dementia, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 foods useful for the health of the pancreas</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/7-foods-useful-for-the-health-of-the-pancreas/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 16:34:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/7-foods-useful-for-the-health-of-the-pancreas/</guid>
      <description>The pancreas plays a key role in the digestion and regulation of blood sugar levels.
The pancreas produces two types of secretions: the first is excreted to the gut, where it secretes a juicer containing digestive enzymes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 Successful Steps to Quit Smoking Electronic Cigarettes</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/9-successful-steps-to-quit-smoking-electronic-cigarettes/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 18:38:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/9-successful-steps-to-quit-smoking-electronic-cigarettes/</guid>
      <description>You may have heard that e-cigarette smoking causes fatal lung disease for its users. If you are ready to quit, these strategies will help.
In her report published by The Healthy website, author Andrea Barbalic said that the dangers of smoking e-cigarettes are becoming more pronounced for medical experts and the general public.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golden tips for winter sports</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/golden-tips-for-winter-sports/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Nov 2019 10:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/golden-tips-for-winter-sports/</guid>
      <description>Exercise is especially useful during winter, as it strengthens the immune system. To take advantage of the benefits of sports, the body should be well protected from the cold by wearing appropriate clothing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to read the results of the blood test?</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/how-to-read-the-results-of-the-blood-test/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 09:59:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/how-to-read-the-results-of-the-blood-test/</guid>
      <description>A blood test is usually performed as part of a comprehensive medical examination or prior to surgical interventions. However, this analysis includes several vague abbreviations such as LDL, GPT or RBC, whose meaning is difficult to interpret.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 facts you do not know about your skeleton</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/6-facts-you-do-not-know-about-your-skeleton/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 11:21:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/6-facts-you-do-not-know-about-your-skeleton/</guid>
      <description>Our bones are known to be living tissue capable of repairing and reshaping themselves in accordance with our daily activity.
Adam Taylor, professor and director of the Center for Clinical Anatomy Education and Rebecca Shepherd, a Ph.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>5 symptoms indicate that you have a problem in your ear</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/5-symptoms-indicate-that-you-have-a-problem-in-your-ear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 11:04:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/5-symptoms-indicate-that-you-have-a-problem-in-your-ear/</guid>
      <description>If you have any of these symptoms you should see your doctor as soon as possible to see if you have a problem with your ears.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What are coffee diseases?</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-are-coffee-diseases/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 07:08:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-are-coffee-diseases/</guid>
      <description>Coffee is a popular drink, and some people say they can&amp;rsquo;t imagine living without it, but drinking too much can lead to &amp;ldquo;caffeine poisoning&amp;rdquo;.
Dr. Walid Sarhan, a Jordanian psychiatrist, says that coffee is a favorite international beverage, which is surpassed only in oil by international trade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 reasons to eat beets daily</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/7-reasons-to-eat-beets-daily/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 06:53:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/7-reasons-to-eat-beets-daily/</guid>
      <description>Beetroot contains a number of important and beneficial substances such as vitamin B, iron, magnesium, and potassium, as well as some nutrients that are available only in a few foods.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 dangerous foods people continue to eat</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/9-dangerous-foods-people-continue-to-eat/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 18:29:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/9-dangerous-foods-people-continue-to-eat/</guid>
      <description>There are dangerous foods that people eat and may lead to death, not only a hamburger provided by some fast-food restaurants or French fries and all products that are high in saturated fat, but there are many other types.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Insomnia may lead to stroke</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/insomnia-may-lead-to-stroke/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 18:11:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/insomnia-may-lead-to-stroke/</guid>
      <description>People with insomnia or intermittent sleep may be more likely to have a heart attack or stroke than people who don&amp;rsquo;t have any sleep problems, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Electronic cigarettes suffocate the heart muscle</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/electronic-cigarettes-suffocate-the-heart-muscle/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2019 14:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/electronic-cigarettes-suffocate-the-heart-muscle/</guid>
      <description>Smoking electronic cigarettes significantly affect the health of the heart by reducing the levels of blood flow in it.
The study was conducted by researchers at the American Heart Association&amp;rsquo;s Tobacco Center and will present its findings to the Society&amp;rsquo;s annual conference, which will be held November 16-18 in Pennsylvania.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Using food .. 6 ways to combat stress and improve mood</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/6-ways-to-combat-stress-and-improve-mood/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 14:13:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/6-ways-to-combat-stress-and-improve-mood/</guid>
      <description>When we are frustrated or stressed, we are eager to eat chocolate to modify our mood. But the truth is that the feeling of chocolate is short-lived, making us worse off than before.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nuts protect you from being overweight</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/nuts-protect-you-from-being-overweight/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 13:55:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/nuts-protect-you-from-being-overweight/</guid>
      <description>NEW YORK (Reuters Health) &amp;ndash; Despite the high-calorie intake of nuts, a daily intake may reduce weight gain, especially when substituting for foods with fewer health benefits, a new study suggests.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleep disorders .. What causes them? Where are the risks?</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/sleep-disorders-causes-and-risks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 13:34:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/sleep-disorders-causes-and-risks/</guid>
      <description>Some people suffer from sleep disorders, what causes them? What are the risks? How can they be confronted?
Dr. Ulrich Fodderholzer says sleep disorders mean an inability to enjoy a restful and comfortable sleep at least three nights a week for more than four weeks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sexually transmitted infections</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/sexually-transmitted-infections/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 10:31:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/sexually-transmitted-infections/</guid>
      <description>Many patients believe that since they&amp;rsquo;ve been with the same partner for many years, they can&amp;rsquo;t get a sexually transmitted infection and therefore they don&amp;rsquo;t need to get tested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The ultimate joints pain guide from zero to finish</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-ultimate-joints-pain-guide-from-zero-to-finish/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2019 21:52:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-ultimate-joints-pain-guide-from-zero-to-finish/</guid>
      <description>One of the most health issues that confront the 21th-century population is joint pain from knee pain to neck pain, ankle, hip or pelvic pain, especially for people who suffer from severe health problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man goes through life without fear due to brain disorder</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/man-goes-through-life-without-fear-due-to-brain-disorder/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Sep 2019 20:33:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/man-goes-through-life-without-fear-due-to-brain-disorder/</guid>
      <description>A U.S 43 years old man declared as F.S from Florida. has a rare genetic condition causing him a brain disease that makes anyone who has this brain disorder absent of fear, they can’t feel anything when they are in a situation that is terrifying for a normal person.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>46 health myths most people believe in</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/46-health-myths-most-people-believe-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Sep 2019 00:47:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/46-health-myths-most-people-believe-in/</guid>
      <description>We all heard at some stage in our lives some advice from our parents, family or friends that we looked after to appear that it is totally false, maybe even the opposite of truth, people to transfer a lot of talk mouth to mouth without checking after it, we tried in this article to compile a list of the most common myths people believe in.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nutrients that may change your health forever and for good</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/nutrients-that-may-change-your-health-forever-and-for-good/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Jul 2019 13:57:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/nutrients-that-may-change-your-health-forever-and-for-good/</guid>
      <description>So we all know that the food that we eat contains calories but looking into it more we could consider calories as energy, we can split the energy into free main types known as macronutrients these free are known as protein carbohydrates and fat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Anorexia -- You will not believe how this eating disorder can transform people</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/anorexia-you-will-not-believe-how-this-eating-disorder-can-transform-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2019 00:08:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/anorexia-you-will-not-believe-how-this-eating-disorder-can-transform-people/</guid>
      <description>Patients with anorexia nervosa the most lethal psychiatric condition feel compelled to diet and exercise despite negative consequences restricting food become automatic and consuming high-calorie foods causes anxiety.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>7 Signs That You May Be Suffering From Vitamin D Deficiency</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/7-signs-that-you-may-be-suffering-from-vitamin-d-deficiency/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 14:59:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/7-signs-that-you-may-be-suffering-from-vitamin-d-deficiency/</guid>
      <description>According to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention (CDC), 32 percent of adults and children in the U.S. are vitamin D deficient. While people get vitamin D from food and sunlight, Dr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What Your Fingernails Say About Your Health</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-your-fingernails-say-about-your-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 08:34:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-your-fingernails-say-about-your-health/</guid>
      <description>Ever wonder why your nails are so brittle, yellow, or otherwise discolored? Though you may not know it, these seemingly harmless symptoms may indicate you have some underlying health issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t Use Or Ingest Ginger If You Have Any of These Four Conditions</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/dont-use-or-ingest-ginger-if-you-have-any-of-these-four-conditions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 08:22:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/dont-use-or-ingest-ginger-if-you-have-any-of-these-four-conditions/</guid>
      <description>Ginger is a highly nutritious plant. In fact, it&amp;rsquo;s widely used as a folk medicine for a number of conditions. That&amp;rsquo;s because its active components, including gingerol and shogaols, have a ton of health benefits to offer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Alarming Symptoms Of Tonsilloliths That Should Never Be Ignored</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/6-alarming-symptoms-of-tonsilloliths-that-should-never-be-ignored/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 09:06:56 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/6-alarming-symptoms-of-tonsilloliths-that-should-never-be-ignored/</guid>
      <description>Ever experience a sore throat but think there could be more to it than having strep throat or tonsillitis? Maybe you&amp;rsquo;ve noticed your tonsils are swollen or you see something strange at the back of your throat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Colon Cancer Survival Rate Is 92% When Caught Early -- Don&#39;t Ignore These 5 Early Warning Signs</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/colon-cancer-survival-rate-is-92-when-caught-early-dont-ignore-these-5-early-warning-signs/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 08:48:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/colon-cancer-survival-rate-is-92-when-caught-early-dont-ignore-these-5-early-warning-signs/</guid>
      <description>Cancers have a way of striking when we least expect them to because they come with symptoms that are very similar to other symptoms that will be experienced.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Woman Wears Mascara To Bed For 25 Years And Never Washes Her Face -- See Under Her Eyelid</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/woman-wears-mascara-to-bed-for-25-years-and-never-washes-her-face-see-under-her-eyelid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 08:36:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/woman-wears-mascara-to-bed-for-25-years-and-never-washes-her-face-see-under-her-eyelid/</guid>
      <description>Most of us wear our makeup to bed on occasion. We may come in and just be too tired to wash it off so we just go to bed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
