<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>entertainment on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/categories/entertainment/</link>
    <description>Recent content in entertainment on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2020 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 12:55:30 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/categories/entertainment/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>10 rules: how to win the League of Legends if your teammates are nerds</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/10-rules-how-to-win-the-league-of-legends-if-your-teammates-are-nerds/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Apr 2020 12:55:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/10-rules-how-to-win-the-league-of-legends-if-your-teammates-are-nerds/</guid>
      <description>That time I played for Rammus. It all started perfectly: in the first few minutes, I twice killed a stranger Ari, ensured a good start for our Lucian and Morgana, and helped to take over Li Sina.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>TOP-16 of the most high-tech types of firearms</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/top-16-of-the-most-high-tech-types-of-firearms/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2020 05:28:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/top-16-of-the-most-high-tech-types-of-firearms/</guid>
      <description>Military men around the world create and test futuristic weapons that look like something from the James Bond movies.
From weapons capable of firing underwater to pistols equipped with a fingerprint recognition system, businessinsider.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Who invented writing?</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/who-invented-writing/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 21:23:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/who-invented-writing/</guid>
      <description>The alphabet we know today is the result of multiple evolutions. The beginnings of this mode of communication, namely rock art, dating back to prehistoric times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;The Massacre of Chios&#34; by Delacroix in detail</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-massacre-of-chios-by-delacroix-in-detail/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 21:18:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-massacre-of-chios-by-delacroix-in-detail/</guid>
      <description>On April 11, 1822, the Turkish army crushed in blood the uprising of the population of the island of Chios. The artist paints his anger.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why have we still not found extraterrestrials?</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/why-have-we-still-not-found-extraterrestrials/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 21:10:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/why-have-we-still-not-found-extraterrestrials/</guid>
      <description>The famous British astrophysicist Stephen Hawking, who died today from Charcot’s disease, was sure of it: life exists elsewhere and we will have proof of it by the end of the century.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mentalists: how do they do it?</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/mentalists-how-do-they-do-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 21:01:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/mentalists-how-do-they-do-it/</guid>
      <description>They read your mind, count, as fast as a calculator, move objects … As you might expect: there is something. Mentalist: a person who uses mental acuity, hypnosis and/or suggestion.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why do we bleed from the nose?</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/why-do-we-bleed-from-the-nose/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 20:51:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/why-do-we-bleed-from-the-nose/</guid>
      <description>Nosebleeds or epistaxis is a mild condition, but can sometimes be a sign of an underlying disease. We sometimes bleed from the nose at night or even in the middle of the day and suddenly enough.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Five women wanted a fresh start, now there are only two left</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/five-women-wanted-a-fresh-start-now-there-are-only-two-left/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 11:04:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/five-women-wanted-a-fresh-start-now-there-are-only-two-left/</guid>
      <description>They wanted to reorganize the migrant cultural center Workshop of Cultures (WdK) &amp;ndash; and now they have obviously failed because of their own visions. Only at the beginning of the year did Louna Sbou, Nina Martin, Nathalie Mba Bikoro, Tmnit Zere, and Saskia Köbschall take over the sponsorship of the WdK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Kings and princes abandoned royal life because of love</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/kings-and-princes-abandoned-royal-life-because-of-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 05:52:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/kings-and-princes-abandoned-royal-life-because-of-love/</guid>
      <description>Through their official account on Instagram, the couple Prince Harry and Meghan Markle announced the “Duke of Sussex” abandoning their royal duties a few days ago, adding that they would educate their son between North America and Britain, and it was reported that Megan would contract with Disney to perform the audio in her films, in addition to her work in the fashion industry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First Responders Decide To Have Some Fun By Making This Upbeat Public Relations Video</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/first-responders-decide-to-have-some-fun-by-making-this-upbeat-public-relations-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 16:25:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/first-responders-decide-to-have-some-fun-by-making-this-upbeat-public-relations-video/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;d think that people who deal with accidents, crime, and death as a part of their job would be rather grim-faced all the time. But, just like the rest of us, they also know the importance of smiling and having fun, which is why the first responders of Rock County, Wisconsin, decided to make this upbeat video.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>These Summertime Life Hacks Are Guaranteed To Give You A Stress-Free Season</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/these-summertime-life-hacks-are-guaranteed-to-give-you-a-stress-free-season/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 16:16:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/these-summertime-life-hacks-are-guaranteed-to-give-you-a-stress-free-season/</guid>
      <description>Now that summer is here, it’s time to start thinking about all that outdoor fun! Barbecues, lazy days by the pool, and weekend beach trips are all made a little easier when you have a few tricks up your sleeve.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What These Rough High School Boys Did On Stage Left The Audience In Total Awe</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-these-rough-high-school-boys-did-on-stage-left-the-audience-in-total-awe/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 16:09:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-these-rough-high-school-boys-did-on-stage-left-the-audience-in-total-awe/</guid>
      <description>High school talent shows are a national pastime. They give everyone in the community a chance to observe the unique talents of their young and aspiring kiddos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What This Man Is Doing For Disabled Dogs In His Hometown Is Simply Heroic</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-this-man-is-doing-for-disabled-dogs-in-his-hometown-is-simply-heroic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 16:04:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-this-man-is-doing-for-disabled-dogs-in-his-hometown-is-simply-heroic/</guid>
      <description>A man in Serbia is giving disabled dogs in his country the chance to run again with the help of the doggy wheelchairs he makes from scratch.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>He Wrapped Something Around The Barrel Of His Gun, Creating This Insane Hack</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/he-wrapped-something-around-the-barrel-of-his-gun-creating-this-insane-hack/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2019 15:55:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/he-wrapped-something-around-the-barrel-of-his-gun-creating-this-insane-hack/</guid>
      <description>Going out in the morning to hunt can leave you quite famished. At 4 a.m., no one wants to actually cook anything. Leave it to these gun-lovers to figure out how to kill two birds with one stone, and end up with some pretty crispy bacon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Everyday Household Item Surprisingly Caused A Terrible Home Fire</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/this-everyday-household-item-surprisingly-caused-a-terrible-home-fire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 03:01:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/this-everyday-household-item-surprisingly-caused-a-terrible-home-fire/</guid>
      <description>Dave&#39; s worst nightmare became a reality when his house was tragically set ablaze by a discarded 9-volt battery. These batteries are normally found in smoke detectors but can cause some serious damage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Boy Was Asked By An Adult To Slap This Girl, But What He Did Instead Is Inspiring</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/a-boy-was-asked-by-an-adult-to-slap-this-girl-but-what-he-did-instead-is-inspiring/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 02:50:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/a-boy-was-asked-by-an-adult-to-slap-this-girl-but-what-he-did-instead-is-inspiring/</guid>
      <description>What happens when you put a boy in front of a girl and ask him to slap her? How will the kid react? Will, he actually do what the adult tells him to do, or will he refuse?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Man Challenges Gaston To A Push-Up Competition, Only To Get A Humbling Surprise</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/man-challenges-gaston-to-a-push-up-competition-only-to-get-a-humbling-surprise/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 02:39:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/man-challenges-gaston-to-a-push-up-competition-only-to-get-a-humbling-surprise/</guid>
      <description>The actor playing Beauty and the Beast’ s Gaston at Disney World in Orlando is known for his bravado, especially after a video of a little girl putting him in his place went viral last month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Watch As An Octopus Stuck In A Jar Unscrews The Lid From The Inside</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/watch-as-an-octopus-stuck-in-a-jar-unscrews-the-lid-from-the-inside/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jun 2019 02:28:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/watch-as-an-octopus-stuck-in-a-jar-unscrews-the-lid-from-the-inside/</guid>
      <description>If you ever wanted to see how an octopus responds in a rather tough situation, you&amp;rsquo;re in luck.
The clip below shows an octopus being placed in a glass jar, with the lid screwed back on tight to close the creature inside.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Girl Gets Scolded By An Abusive Teacher, Only To Kick Him In The Crotch</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/little-girl-gets-scolded-by-an-abusive-teacher-only-to-kick-him-in-the-crotch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 21:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/little-girl-gets-scolded-by-an-abusive-teacher-only-to-kick-him-in-the-crotch/</guid>
      <description>This aggressive teacher in Russia will probably think twice before humiliating another kid in his class again. He was rightfully put in his place after one little girl kicked him in the groin for his abusive behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Doctors Believed That Their Prematurely Born Baby Would Die, But This Miracle Happened</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/doctors-believed-that-their-prematurely-born-baby-would-die-but-this-miracle-happened/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 21:09:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/doctors-believed-that-their-prematurely-born-baby-would-die-but-this-miracle-happened/</guid>
      <description>Kate Ogg and her husband David were thrilled to be told that, after years of trying to get pregnant, they were going to have two babies!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This May Look Like A Colorful Mess, But Just Watch What Happens To It</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/this-may-look-like-a-colorful-mess-but-just-watch-what-happens-to-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 20:45:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/this-may-look-like-a-colorful-mess-but-just-watch-what-happens-to-it/</guid>
      <description>Food should be fun. This is especially true for cakes and desserts. Yet no dessert is as much fun to make as this groovy and colorful cake.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>By Mixing Peanut Butter And Honey, You Can Create A Simple And Delicious Treat</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/by-mixing-peanut-butter-and-honey-you-can-create-a-simple-and-delicious-treat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 20:32:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/by-mixing-peanut-butter-and-honey-you-can-create-a-simple-and-delicious-treat/</guid>
      <description>Granola bars are always a great option for an afternoon snack. They are quick, tasty, and healthy (well, most of the time). Some of the cheaper, store-bought bars contain a ton of high fructose corn syrup.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
