<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Israel on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/israel/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Israel on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2024 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 13:19:11 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/israel/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Israel on the way to new elections in March</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-on-the-way-to-new-elections-in-march/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 13:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-on-the-way-to-new-elections-in-march/</guid>
      <description>Israelis will go to the polls for the third time in a year. Polls again give Netanyahu and his rival Gantz neck and neck.
The Israeli political class was preparing the ground Wednesday evening for new elections, at the beginning of March, the third in less than a year, with the flavor of a new duel between Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, now charged with corruption, and his rival Benny Gantz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Israel deports Human Rights Watch director</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-deports-human-rights-watch-director/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2019 19:08:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-deports-human-rights-watch-director/</guid>
      <description>Omar Shaker, director of Human Rights Watch in Israel and Palestine, left in response to Tel Aviv&amp;rsquo;s decision to deport him.
The organization held a press conference in the presence of the CEO asserted that Shaker will continue to work from abroad to document all violations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>After targeting sites in Syria, Israel is preparing for an Iranian strike</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-is-preparing-for-an-iranian-strike/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 10:51:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-is-preparing-for-an-iranian-strike/</guid>
      <description>JERUSALEM (Reuters) &amp;ndash; Tel Aviv is preparing for a possible missile strike by Iranian forces in Syria in the coming hours or days in response to a dawn attack on its positions near Damascus that it said belonged to the Iranian Qods Force, Israeli security sources said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>America supports settlement building in the West Bank</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/america-supports-settlement-building-in-the-west-bank/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 07:31:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/america-supports-settlement-building-in-the-west-bank/</guid>
      <description>The European Union has made clear that it continues to believe that Israeli settlement activity in the Occupied Palestinian Territories is illegal under international law and reduces the chances of lasting peace, in response to Washington&amp;rsquo;s support for Tel Aviv in building settlements.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Israel and Iran: dangerous vortex and deterrence</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-and-iran-dangerous-vortex-and-deterrence/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 11:58:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-and-iran-dangerous-vortex-and-deterrence/</guid>
      <description>In the face of Hezbollah, which is building a new front, and the Iranian threat, whose nature is changing from time to time, the Israeli army is building a concrete wall and advanced observation posts near the northern border, in a constant battle between parade and deterrence.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
