<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Netanyahu on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/netanyahu/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Netanyahu on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2020 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 12:20:38 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/netanyahu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Israel&#39;s Netanyahu accused of exploiting virus crisis</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israels-netanyahu-accused-of-exploiting-virus-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Mar 2020 12:20:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israels-netanyahu-accused-of-exploiting-virus-crisis/</guid>
      <description>JERUSALEM (AP) &amp;mdash; With the Israeli government enacting a series of emergency measures to stem the spread of the new coronavirus, Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu is facing growing accusations that he is exploiting the crisis to entrench himself in power and undermining the country&amp;rsquo;s democratic foundations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exit polls: Netanyahu just short of majority in Israel vote</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/exit-polls-netanyahu-just-short-of-majority-in-israel-vote/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 22:17:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/exit-polls-netanyahu-just-short-of-majority-in-israel-vote/</guid>
      <description>JERUSALEM (AP) &amp;mdash; Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu held a solid edge over his main rival in Israel&amp;rsquo;s third election in beneath a 365 days, exit polls indicated Monday night, but it undoubtedly used to be unclear whether he can clinch the parliamentary majority wished to direct victory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Israel on the way to new elections in March</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-on-the-way-to-new-elections-in-march/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 13:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-on-the-way-to-new-elections-in-march/</guid>
      <description>Israelis will go to the polls for the third time in a year. Polls again give Netanyahu and his rival Gantz neck and neck.
The Israeli political class was preparing the ground Wednesday evening for new elections, at the beginning of March, the third in less than a year, with the flavor of a new duel between Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, now charged with corruption, and his rival Benny Gantz.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
