<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>lifestyle on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/categories/lifestyle/</link>
    <description>Recent content in lifestyle on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2024 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 16:39:49 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/categories/lifestyle/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What to do when you hate your job</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-to-do-when-you-hate-your-job/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Feb 2020 16:39:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-to-do-when-you-hate-your-job/</guid>
      <description>Do you sometimes feel that you hate your job and have the feeling that you are the only one who suffers from this matter, while everyone around you seems to be occupying the job of their dreams, well this is a wrong feeling, only Gallup site about 85% of employees and workers around the world hate their jobs, for various reasons?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How State Marriage and Divorce Rates Stack Up</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/how-state-marriage-and-divorce-rates-stack-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 22:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/how-state-marriage-and-divorce-rates-stack-up/</guid>
      <description>National Marriage, Divorce Rates Both Declined in the Last 10 Years From 2008 to 2018, national marriage and divorce rates declined. However, both rates vary by state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Learn to gain charisma and Become more attractive</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/learn-to-gain-charisma-and-become-more-attractive/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 21:47:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/learn-to-gain-charisma-and-become-more-attractive/</guid>
      <description>There is a popular belief that successful people in life possess charisma, due to the many examples of distinguished and prominent people in society, thanks to their possession of this trait.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random Acts of Kindness Day 2020 -- what will you do ?</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/random-acts-of-kindness-day-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Feb 2020 11:39:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/random-acts-of-kindness-day-2020/</guid>
      <description>Today look outside of yourself and give a demonstration of grace. It tends to be more odd or a relative. Simply show somebody you care enough to give them a grin or some promising words.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>China 2020 Valentine&#39;s Day a how to</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/china-2020-valentines-day/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 15:52:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/china-2020-valentines-day/</guid>
      <description>Valentine’s Day in 2020 and the epidemic is not over yet. Two people cannot meet to eat, watch movies, as before. Many lovers ca n&amp;rsquo;t even meet at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How win a journey around the world at the lowest cost</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/how-win-a-journey-around-the-world-at-the-lowest-cost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Feb 2020 13:19:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/how-win-a-journey-around-the-world-at-the-lowest-cost/</guid>
      <description>In spite of the images and experiences infested with social networking sites for those who decided to travel around the world and enjoy learning about different cultures, the dream of travel we see is a crazy dream that remains unattainable despite the existence of companies that help in this and the presence of what deserves adventure around the world, and therefore we gathered everything you need if I decided to take a trip that could last for months around the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Express your love for yourself and take care of your mental and emotional health</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/express-your-love-for-yourself-and-take-care-of-your-mental-and-emotional-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Feb 2020 13:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/express-your-love-for-yourself-and-take-care-of-your-mental-and-emotional-health/</guid>
      <description>Mental and emotional health should not be confused with happiness and usually maintaining a good mood, because strong mental health does not guarantee you to be happy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Here are 5 tricks to raise your productivity if working on your own or from home</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/here-are-5-tricks-to-raise-your-productivity-if-working-on-your-own-or-from-home/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 05:29:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/here-are-5-tricks-to-raise-your-productivity-if-working-on-your-own-or-from-home/</guid>
      <description>Self-employment is now gaining more importance, but private work is not easy, especially when it is from home. Although self-employment is tempting, it is not without problems, the person may face higher tax burdens and bureaucratic obstacles, as well as a sense of economic instability.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Do emotions have the same meaning around the world</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/do-emotions-have-the-same-meaning-around-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 19:30:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/do-emotions-have-the-same-meaning-around-the-world/</guid>
      <description>The debate between culture and biology – with regard to our emotions – has a prominent place in scientific and philosophical discoveries, there are those who suggest that some feelings have left an evolutionary imprint in the neural biological structure of the human race, while others see that far from being global, emotions are cultural structures that we learn their meanings Of social inferences.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Compulsive shopping mania</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/compulsive-shopping-mania/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Dec 2019 09:40:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/compulsive-shopping-mania/</guid>
      <description>For most people, shopping is a balanced tour between seduction and necessity, but about 6% of young people, mostly women, face the inferno of “compulsive shopping” that dominates their lives and can damage their budgets.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to save money during seasons and holidays</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/how-to-save-money-during-seasons-and-holidays/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Dec 2019 12:40:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/how-to-save-money-during-seasons-and-holidays/</guid>
      <description>The holiday and holiday season is related to spending a lot of money and it is time to enjoy food and drinks, but people are looking forward to learning how to better manage their money on these occasions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 questions that lead you to success and happiness during 2020</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/10-questions-that-lead-you-to-success-and-happiness-during-2020/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 17:47:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/10-questions-that-lead-you-to-success-and-happiness-during-2020/</guid>
      <description>With the year 2020 and the new decade drawing fast, many of us are taking advantage of the year-end period to reflect on where we are now and look forward to the things we hope to achieve in the future.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips for choosing a last-minute gift that everyone likes</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tips-for-choosing-a-last-minute-gift-that-everyone-likes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 25 Dec 2019 06:58:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tips-for-choosing-a-last-minute-gift-that-everyone-likes/</guid>
      <description>Buying a gift well thought out is important, especially if you are sure that it will be liked by the person you will give it to, but you may be in trouble and not know what gift to buy for someone you know, especially while you know that time is running out of you.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t do these things just to please others</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/dont-do-these-things-just-to-please-others/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Dec 2019 04:49:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/dont-do-these-things-just-to-please-others/</guid>
      <description>We often try to show that we are perfect to be loved and accepted by society, but no one is perfect, and we cannot please everyone around us, nor should we try to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scientifically, living near the sea preserves mental health</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/scientifically-living-near-the-sea-preserves-mental-health/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2019 19:30:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/scientifically-living-near-the-sea-preserves-mental-health/</guid>
      <description>People who live near the coast are usually happier than those who live in landlocked cities, and this is the conclusion of a recent study by researchers from the University of Exeter and published in the magazine Health and Place in September 2019.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Improve the performance of the mind and Protect your memory from early Alzheimer&#39;s</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/improve-the-performance-of-the-mind-and-protect-your-memory-from-early-alzheimers/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Dec 2019 18:05:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/improve-the-performance-of-the-mind-and-protect-your-memory-from-early-alzheimers/</guid>
      <description>Brain training has already become a trend, especially after the emergence of appropriate courses and programs aimed at spreading this approach between people.
The mind is just like the body, the brain needs training in order to grow and remain in good condition, to protect our cognitive abilities from deterioration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are rich people happier than other people?</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/are-rich-people-happier-than-other-people/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Dec 2019 10:38:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/are-rich-people-happier-than-other-people/</guid>
      <description>A study conducted in the Netherlands said that there is a positive relationship between wealth and contentment in life, and this is not surprising. But, interestingly enough, the experience of happiness enjoyed by the wealthy may stem largely from how they spend their time and not on the things that they buy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>8 logical reasons explain why you have to love your enemies</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/8-logical-reasons-explain-why-you-have-to-love-your-enemies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 17:09:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/8-logical-reasons-explain-why-you-have-to-love-your-enemies/</guid>
      <description>The development of the enemy is sometimes attributed to the differences in the characters and events that led to it, and sometimes other people end up hating you for no reason at all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Are you an introvert? Investing in business is the road to success</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/are-you-an-introvert-investing-in-business-is-the-road-to-success/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 17:00:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/are-you-an-introvert-investing-in-business-is-the-road-to-success/</guid>
      <description>It is easy to imagine that introverts see their qualities as an obstacle in their careers, especially when our culture glorifies the hustle and charisma.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Staying within your comfort zone makes you live a life free of excitement</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/staying-within-your-comfort-zone-makes-you-live-a-life-free-of-excitement/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 14:06:04 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/staying-within-your-comfort-zone-makes-you-live-a-life-free-of-excitement/</guid>
      <description>Whether your concerns are about the fate of your relationship, your career, your death, or uneasiness about something, insistence on staying within your comfort zone will make you live a limited life without risk and excitement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips for protection from radiation of smartphones</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tips-for-protection-from-radiation-of-smartphones/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Dec 2019 13:39:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tips-for-protection-from-radiation-of-smartphones/</guid>
      <description>The German Federal Office for Radiation Protection has recommended some preventive measures to protect against the risk of radiation from smartphones.
German experts explained that the first of these measures is not to use mobile phones in places where the network is weakened: the weaker the telephone network, the greater the need to operate the phone more powerful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Japanese way of living in inner peace</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-japanese-way-of-living-in-inner-peace/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 20:39:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-japanese-way-of-living-in-inner-peace/</guid>
      <description>To be happy for many people, maybe the only goal of their lives. We all seek to find a way to enjoy, either by avoiding contact with each other and seeking to improve social status, by acquiring a large bank account, by filling life with experience, or by leaving a creative legacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 university degrees are required during the next decade</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/10-university-degrees-are-required-during-the-next-decade/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2019 16:53:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/10-university-degrees-are-required-during-the-next-decade/</guid>
      <description>Which undergraduate degrees will be in demand during the 1920s?
According to the US Bureau of Labor Statistics, there is a growing demand for some disciplines in the United States, and accordingly, students are directed to study them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>WISE Conference in Doha: Artificial Intelligence Will Change the Future of Education in the World</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/artificial-intelligence-will-change-the-future-of-education-in-the-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 10:20:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/artificial-intelligence-will-change-the-future-of-education-in-the-world/</guid>
      <description>What form of education looks forward? Will artificial intelligence eliminate the role of teachers? Such questions and others were the subjects of the interventions of participants at the WISE 10th World Education Innovation Summit on Wednesday, entitled &amp;ldquo;Learn again, what does it mean to be a human being?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How stress and pressure can change our lives for the better</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/how-stress-and-pressure-can-change-our-lives-for-the-better/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 11:11:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/how-stress-and-pressure-can-change-our-lives-for-the-better/</guid>
      <description>Tensions became a common feature in the 21st century, causing a mental health crisis, and science suggests that it affected unborn babies.
In contrast, psychologists are keen to teach us that there is some kind of good, healthy and even fruitful tension.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>9 signs tell you that your marriage will not exceed the obstacle of the seventh year</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/9-signs-tell-you-that-your-marriage-will-not-exceed-the-obstacle-of-the-seventh-year/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 07:49:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/9-signs-tell-you-that-your-marriage-will-not-exceed-the-obstacle-of-the-seventh-year/</guid>
      <description>Have you heard about the &amp;ldquo;seventh-year obstacle?&amp;rdquo; It is basically an idea that couples tend to break away during the seventh year of their marriage, where one or both spouses begin to feel malaise, skepticism, and dissatisfaction with the relationship.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Study says the higher the intelligence of a man the less likely betrayal of his partner</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/study-says-the-higher-the-intelligence-of-a-man-the-less-likely-betrayal-of-his-partner/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2019 07:36:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/study-says-the-higher-the-intelligence-of-a-man-the-less-likely-betrayal-of-his-partner/</guid>
      <description>When talking about moral values, they often mention fulfillment. In fact, an honest and loyal person is trustworthy and honest, but fulfillment is not tied to having a high level of intelligence.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sarah Arenson .. Judaism that brought down the Ottoman Empire</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/sarah-arenson-judaism-that-brought-down-the-ottoman-empire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 12:17:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/sarah-arenson-judaism-that-brought-down-the-ottoman-empire/</guid>
      <description>In July 1914, World War I broke out, when the assassination of Austrian Crown Prince Archduke Franz Ferdinand and his wife, in Sarajevo, sparked the war.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A world full of enslavers and criminals .. Unknown crimes in the high oceans</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/a-world-full-of-enslavers-and-criminals-unknown-crimes-in-the-high-oceans/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Oct 2019 12:07:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/a-world-full-of-enslavers-and-criminals-unknown-crimes-in-the-high-oceans/</guid>
      <description>French newspaper Le Figaro has reviewed a book by journalist Ian Urbina, who was fortunate to carry out an investigation into outlaws on the high seas, after two years of work as a reporter for The New York Times, and then another two years in which he left the newspaper and funded his investigations through the publisher of his book.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oscar dream evaporates .. Cinema theaters reject the &#34;Irish&#34; film</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/oscar-dream-evaporates-cinema-theaters-reject-the-irish-film/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 12:48:03 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/oscar-dream-evaporates-cinema-theaters-reject-the-irish-film/</guid>
      <description>Netflix executives were surprised to announce that major cinema chains were reluctant to release their upcoming film The Irishman a few weeks before its release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Social media celebrities become millionaires this his how they changed marketing landscape</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/social-media-celebrities-become-millionaires-this-his-how-they-changed-marketing-landscape/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 19:00:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/social-media-celebrities-become-millionaires-this-his-how-they-changed-marketing-landscape/</guid>
      <description>To reach a wide audience, brands are devoting an increasing share of their advertising budgets to social networking sites led by young icons that help shape a new sales culture.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The anniversary of the death of Guevara</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-anniversary-of-the-death-of-guevara/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 12:12:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-anniversary-of-the-death-of-guevara/</guid>
      <description>Today, October 9, is the 52nd anniversary of the departure of the Argentinian activist Che Guevara, one of the most important revolutionary and political faces, which has become an icon of the political and human struggle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 strange information about the Nobel Prize</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/10-strange-information-about-the-nobel-prize/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 11:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/10-strange-information-about-the-nobel-prize/</guid>
      <description>The eyes of the world are turning to Sweden this week, awaiting the completion of the winners of the Nobel Prizes, the most famous and exciting competition.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 Crafting Staples to Make Spooktacular DIY Halloween Decorations</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/4-crafting-staples-to-make-spooktacular-diy-halloween-decorations/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 08:11:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/4-crafting-staples-to-make-spooktacular-diy-halloween-decorations/</guid>
      <description>Spookifying your house with fun Halloween decorations is always a great time, but did you know it could be cheap and simple as well? Maybe you&amp;rsquo;re setting up for a party, or looking for something fun to do with the kids that will get them in the Halloween spirit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Amazon Products You Never Knew You … or Anyone … Needed</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/amazon-products-you-never-knew-you-or-anyone-needed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 08:03:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/amazon-products-you-never-knew-you-or-anyone-needed/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s not hyperbole to say that Amazon has completely changed the retail marketplace forever. The site has opened up retail to anyone with internet access. Along with that, however, it&amp;rsquo;s given every kind of product under the sun a marketplace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Giant House Cats That Aren&#39;t Kittens Anymore</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/giant-house-cats-that-arent-kittens-anymore/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2019 07:45:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/giant-house-cats-that-arent-kittens-anymore/</guid>
      <description>You remember the day like it was yesterday. You just got your brand new kitten. The tiny awkward steps and the pipsqueak meows. He or she was just the tiniest, cutest thing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Diet Doesn&#39;t Just Help With Weight Loss. It May Also Prevent Major Diseases.</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/this-diet-doesnt-just-help-with-weight-loss-it-may-also-prevent-major-diseases/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2019 09:23:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/this-diet-doesnt-just-help-with-weight-loss-it-may-also-prevent-major-diseases/</guid>
      <description>If you have friends or family members who&amp;rsquo;ve lost weight or are very focused on their health, chances are you&amp;rsquo;ve heard of the ketogenic diet. As those who&amp;rsquo;ve adopted the low-carb, high-fat diet will tell you, it comes with many health benefits, especially when it comes to dropping extra pounds.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>This Little Known Place Way Up North Is Perfection. And I Had No Idea It Even Existed Til Now.</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/this-little-known-place-way-up-north-is-perfection-and-i-had-no-idea-it-even-existed-til-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jun 2019 01:36:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/this-little-known-place-way-up-north-is-perfection-and-i-had-no-idea-it-even-existed-til-now/</guid>
      <description>Lapland, Finland, has got to be one of the most beautiful places on earth. Plus, if Santa is real, then he definitely lives in this magical place.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>6 Experiences You Need Before You Die</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/6-experiences-you-need-before-you-die/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Mar 2018 15:03:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/6-experiences-you-need-before-you-die/</guid>
      <description>The world is full of natural wonders; there are so many that it&amp;rsquo;s hard to just exactly what to see. That&amp;rsquo;s why we think it&amp;rsquo;s more important to identify what experiences you want to have before you leave this world.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
