<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>US on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/us/</link>
    <description>Recent content in US on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2020 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 14:37:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/us/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Trump In India And What He&#39;s Doing That The MSM Isn&#39;t Telling You</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-in-india-and-what-hes-doing-that-the-msm-isnt-telling-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 14:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-in-india-and-what-hes-doing-that-the-msm-isnt-telling-you/</guid>
      <description>Namaste, that actually means hi in Indiana, don’t worry I’m not turning a full hippie-dippie, but anyway, Donald Trump officially retweeted upon the announcement of his visit to India which we will be breaking down the significance of geopolitically, especially with all the incredible news happening around American foreign policy including the latest information about the Afghanistan Taliban peace deal that you’re not hearing about in the mainstream media, the extremely messy situation unfolding right now in Syria with Turkey Russia and China is very involved in what looks like a situation that will soon escalate to very dangerous proportions, and then, of course, we’re also gonna be talking about China Philippines there is, of course, a lot more all specifically surrounding American hegemony foreign policy, geopolitical updates that of course, you won’t hear from MSM, so I mean you don’t even hear about the topic of foreign policy being discussed in the presidential debates but it is a key important factor since American foreign policy is essentially policy of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How State Marriage and Divorce Rates Stack Up</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/how-state-marriage-and-divorce-rates-stack-up/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2020 22:24:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/how-state-marriage-and-divorce-rates-stack-up/</guid>
      <description>National Marriage, Divorce Rates Both Declined in the Last 10 Years From 2008 to 2018, national marriage and divorce rates declined. However, both rates vary by state.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump mocked by Trudeau&#39;s mockery alongside Macron and Johnson</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/donald-trump-mocked-by-trudeaus-mockery-alongside-macron-and-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 17:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/donald-trump-mocked-by-trudeaus-mockery-alongside-macron-and-johnson/</guid>
      <description>The US president did not appreciate the words of his Canadian counterpart in an informal conversation, captured Tuesday evening by Anglo-Saxon media.
The tone was informal, the faces relaxed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns and Kurds mobilize .. List of the latest developments of the Turkish operation in Syria</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/russia-warns-and-kurds-mobilize-list-of-the-latest-developments-of-the-turkish-operation-in-syria/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 12:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/russia-warns-and-kurds-mobilize-list-of-the-latest-developments-of-the-turkish-operation-in-syria/</guid>
      <description>Turkish troops are preparing to launch a military operation in northern Syria with the aim of keeping Kurdish fighters out of their borders and establishing a safe area, enabling Syrian refugees to return home.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
