<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Virus on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/virus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Virus on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2020 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 20:17:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/virus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>US virus testing faces new headwind: Lab supply shortages</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/us-virus-testing-faces-new-headwind-lab-supply-shortages/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 20:17:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/us-virus-testing-faces-new-headwind-lab-supply-shortages/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;mdash; First, some of the coronavirus tests didn&amp;rsquo;t work. Then there weren&amp;rsquo;t enough to go around. Now, just as the federal government tries to ramp up nationwide screening, laboratory workers are warning of a new roadblock: dire shortages of testing supplies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Italy&#39;s virus epicenter grapples with huge toll, some hidden</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/italys-virus-epicenter-grapples-with-huge-toll-some-hidden/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Mar 2020 11:20:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/italys-virus-epicenter-grapples-with-huge-toll-some-hidden/</guid>
      <description>BERGAMO, Italy (AP) &amp;mdash; The priest gave a final benediction. There were no flowers, no embraces. Francesca Steffanoni and her mother hurried away from Bergamo&amp;rsquo;s main cemetery, their furtive farewell lasting no more than 5 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sex workers face ruin amid virus fears, brothel closures</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/sex-workers-face-ruin-amid-virus-fears-brothel-closures/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 11:22:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/sex-workers-face-ruin-amid-virus-fears-brothel-closures/</guid>
      <description>BERLIN (AP) &amp;mdash; It&amp;rsquo;s 7 p.m. on a Friday night, a time when Aurel Johannes Marx&amp;rsquo;s three-room brothel on the edge of Berlin would normally be preparing for its first customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virus fears fuel spike in sales of guns and ammunition</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-fears-fuel-spike-in-sales-of-guns-and-ammunition/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 21:22:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-fears-fuel-spike-in-sales-of-guns-and-ammunition/</guid>
      <description>BOISE, Idaho (AP) &amp;mdash; The world&amp;rsquo;s largest gun store, in metro Atlanta, has had lines that are six and eight people deep. A gun store in Los Angeles had lines that stretched down the block.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virus toll in Iran climbs as lockdowns deepen across Mideast</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-toll-in-iran-climbs-as-lockdowns-deepen-across-mideast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 12:17:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-toll-in-iran-climbs-as-lockdowns-deepen-across-mideast/</guid>
      <description>TEHRAN, Iran (AP) &amp;mdash; Iran reported another 129 fatalities from the new coronavirus on Monday, the largest one-day rise in deaths since it began battling the Middle East&amp;rsquo;s worst outbreak, which has claimed more than 850 lives and infected a number of senior officials in the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Despite virus risk, 2020 hopefuls keep up campaigns for now</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/despite-virus-risk-2020-hopefuls-keep-up-campaigns-for-now/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 21:19:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/despite-virus-risk-2020-hopefuls-keep-up-campaigns-for-now/</guid>
      <description>GRAND RAPIDS, Mich. (AP) &amp;mdash; As the coronavirus hits more states, Democratic presidential candidate Bernie Sanders said Sunday his campaign is gauging when it may become necessary to cancel the large campaign rallies that public health experts say could be breeding grounds to spread the potentially deadly illness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virus halts pilgrimages to Mecca, Friday prayers in Iran</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-halts-pilgrimages-to-mecca-friday-prayers-in-iran/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 17:20:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-halts-pilgrimages-to-mecca-friday-prayers-in-iran/</guid>
      <description>TEHRAN, Iran (AP) &amp;mdash; The coronavirus outbreak disrupted Islamic treasure in the Middle East as Saudi Arabia on Wednesday banned its voters and other residents of the kingdom from performing the pilgrimage in Mecca, whereas Iran canceled Friday prayers in principal cities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virus spread prompts Fed to slash rates in surprise move</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-spread-prompts-fed-to-slash-rates-in-surprise-move/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 18:26:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-spread-prompts-fed-to-slash-rates-in-surprise-move/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;mdash; In a shock switch, the Federal Reserve slash its benchmark hobby rate by a good half-percentage point Tuesday as a ability to beef up the financial system within the face of the spreading coronavirus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virus alarms sound worldwide, but China sees crisis ebbing</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-alarms-sound-worldwide-but-china-sees-crisis-ebbing/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2020 07:19:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-alarms-sound-worldwide-but-china-sees-crisis-ebbing/</guid>
      <description>BEIJING (AP) &amp;mdash; Iranians hoarded medical gives, Italians entreated medical doctors out of retirement and South Koreans ready to pump billions into reduction efforts Tuesday because the virus epidemic firmed its lend a hand all the absolute best method by method of the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virus kills member of council advising Iran&#39;s supreme leader</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-kills-member-of-council-advising-irans-supreme-leader/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Mar 2020 12:23:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-kills-member-of-council-advising-irans-supreme-leader/</guid>
      <description>TEHRAN, Iran (AP) &amp;mdash; A member of a council that advises Iran&amp;rsquo;s supreme leader died Monday after falling unwell from the fresh coronavirus, dispute radio reported, turning into the first high first rate to succumb to the sickness that has effects on members of the Islamic Republic&amp;rsquo;s management.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virus cases in Italy soar 40%; US urges Americans not to go</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-cases-in-italy-soar-40-us-urges-americans-not-to-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 19:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-cases-in-italy-soar-40-us-urges-americans-not-to-go/</guid>
      <description>MILAN (AP) &amp;mdash; The replacement of of us infected in Italy with the new coronavirus rose 40% to 1,576 in only 24 hours, Italian authorities offered Sunday, including that five more infected of us had died.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Wash. state sees 1st virus death in US, declares emergency</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/wash-state-sees-1st-virus-death-in-us-declares-emergency/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 03:20:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/wash-state-sees-1st-virus-death-in-us-declares-emergency/</guid>
      <description>The governor of Washington declared a convey of emergency Saturday after a person died there of COVID-19, the first such reported death in the US. Extra than 50 of us in a nursing facility are sick and being examined for the virus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virus effects take hold as Trump calls criticisms a ‘hoax&#39;</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-effects-take-hold-as-trump-calls-criticisms-a-hoax/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 08:20:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-effects-take-hold-as-trump-calls-criticisms-a-hoax/</guid>
      <description>TOKYO (AP) &amp;mdash; The coronavirus outbreak&amp;rsquo;s affect on the arena economy grew extra alarming on Saturday, even as President Donald Trump denounced criticisms of his response to the threat as a &amp;ldquo;hoax&amp;rdquo; cooked up by his political enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virus epidemic growing by day hits schools, concerts, parks</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-epidemic-growing-by-day-hits-schools-concerts-parks/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 10:27:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-epidemic-growing-by-day-hits-schools-concerts-parks/</guid>
      <description>TOKYO (AP) &amp;mdash; Japan&amp;rsquo;s schools ready to cease for nearly a month and entertainers, topped by Okay-pop superstars BTS, canceled events as an outbreak epidemic extended its unfold thru Asia into Europe and on Friday, into sub-Saharan Africa.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In scramble to stop virus, testing raises tough questions</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/in-scramble-to-stop-virus-testing-raises-tough-questions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 01:17:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/in-scramble-to-stop-virus-testing-raises-tough-questions/</guid>
      <description>NEW YORK (AP) &amp;mdash; Health officials confronted complicated questions and doubts Thursday about testing to intercept the short-spreading virus, with scrutiny centered on a four-day lengthen in screening an contaminated California girl despite her doctors&#39; early calls to form so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Stocks go on a wild ride as virus threatens economic damage</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/stocks-go-on-a-wild-ride-as-virus-threatens-economic-damage/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 20:22:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/stocks-go-on-a-wild-ride-as-virus-threatens-economic-damage/</guid>
      <description>NEW YORK (AP) &amp;mdash; Shares went on a wild trip Thursday as traders battle to gauge the aptitude affect of the coronavirus outbreak on the arena economy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Virus response in Mideast tainted by political views of Iran</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-response-in-mideast-tainted-by-political-views-of-iran/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 16:20:14 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/virus-response-in-mideast-tainted-by-political-views-of-iran/</guid>
      <description>BEIRUT (AP) &amp;mdash; Within the Middle East, even virus outbreaks are political.
The coronavirus has killed 26 americans in Iran &amp;mdash; the wonderful toll outdoors of China where it originated.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
