<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Turkey on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/turkey/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Turkey on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2020 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 10:19:48 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/turkey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Turkey vows justice for migrant killed at border with Greece</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/turkey-vows-justice-for-migrant-killed-at-border-with-greece/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Mar 2020 10:19:48 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/turkey-vows-justice-for-migrant-killed-at-border-with-greece/</guid>
      <description>ANKARA, Turkey (AP) &amp;mdash; Turkey has vowed to seek justice for a migrant it says was killed on the border with Greece after Greek authorities fired tear gas and stun grenades to push back dozens of people attempting to cross over.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey raises death toll to 33 troops in Syrian airstrike</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/turkey-raises-death-toll-to-33-troops-in-syrian-airstrike/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 08:24:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/turkey-raises-death-toll-to-33-troops-in-syrian-airstrike/</guid>
      <description>ANKARA, Turkey (AP) &amp;mdash; Turkey on Friday raised the loss of life toll from a Syrian authorities airstrike on its forces in northwestern Syria the outdated night to 33 Turkish troops, the ideal number of Turkish troopers killed in a single day since Ankara first intervened within the Syrian battle in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump In India And What He&#39;s Doing That The MSM Isn&#39;t Telling You</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-in-india-and-what-hes-doing-that-the-msm-isnt-telling-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 14:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-in-india-and-what-hes-doing-that-the-msm-isnt-telling-you/</guid>
      <description>Namaste, that actually means hi in Indiana, don’t worry I’m not turning a full hippie-dippie, but anyway, Donald Trump officially retweeted upon the announcement of his visit to India which we will be breaking down the significance of geopolitically, especially with all the incredible news happening around American foreign policy including the latest information about the Afghanistan Taliban peace deal that you’re not hearing about in the mainstream media, the extremely messy situation unfolding right now in Syria with Turkey Russia and China is very involved in what looks like a situation that will soon escalate to very dangerous proportions, and then, of course, we’re also gonna be talking about China Philippines there is, of course, a lot more all specifically surrounding American hegemony foreign policy, geopolitical updates that of course, you won’t hear from MSM, so I mean you don’t even hear about the topic of foreign policy being discussed in the presidential debates but it is a key important factor since American foreign policy is essentially policy of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ankara warns of a new operation in Syria if Washington and Moscow fail to honor their commitments</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/ankara-warns-of-a-new-operation-in-syria-if-washington-and-moscow-fail-to-honor-their-commitments/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2019 07:45:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/ankara-warns-of-a-new-operation-in-syria-if-washington-and-moscow-fail-to-honor-their-commitments/</guid>
      <description>Turkish Foreign Minister Mevlut Cavusoglu said that the United States and Russia did not do what is necessary under the agreements on northern Syria, stressing the need to do so.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia sends 300 additional troops to the Syrian-Turkish border</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/russia-sends-300-additional-troops-to-the-syrian-turkish-border/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 21:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/russia-sends-300-additional-troops-to-the-syrian-turkish-border/</guid>
      <description>The Russian Defense Ministry announced the arrival of about 300 Russian military police to Syria to help the withdrawal of Kurdish forces from the border with Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s policy in Syria could reorganize the state</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trumps-policy-in-syria-could-reorganize-the-state/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 12:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trumps-policy-in-syria-could-reorganize-the-state/</guid>
      <description>US President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;reactionary&amp;rdquo; foreign policy would bring the Islamic State back to Syria, writer Kim Seggupta says.
One of the hallmarks of Trump&amp;rsquo;s foreign policy is his lack of success against adversaries and his failure to stand by allies, the writer adds in an article in The Independent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continued international reactions to the Turkish military operation in Syria</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/continued-international-reactions-to-the-turkish-military-operation-in-syria/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 18:41:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/continued-international-reactions-to-the-turkish-military-operation-in-syria/</guid>
      <description>International reactions to Turkey&amp;rsquo;s launch on Wednesday of a large-scale military operation in northeast Syria to develop a safe zone evolved. France and the Netherlands summoned their ambassadors to protest against the military attack, while Iran called on Turkey to immediately halt the military operation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkish&#39;s special Forces units continue to advance in the eastern Euphrates region</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/special-forces-units-continue-to-advance-in-the-eastern-euphrates/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 10:57:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/special-forces-units-continue-to-advance-in-the-eastern-euphrates/</guid>
      <description>This came in a statement published by the ministry on the operation launched by Turkey on Wednesday northeastern Syria, with a statement attached to the scenes of the progress of these forces.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns and Kurds mobilize .. List of the latest developments of the Turkish operation in Syria</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/russia-warns-and-kurds-mobilize-list-of-the-latest-developments-of-the-turkish-operation-in-syria/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 12:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/russia-warns-and-kurds-mobilize-list-of-the-latest-developments-of-the-turkish-operation-in-syria/</guid>
      <description>Turkish troops are preparing to launch a military operation in northern Syria with the aim of keeping Kurdish fighters out of their borders and establishing a safe area, enabling Syrian refugees to return home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Kurds and the Syria Crisis From the Equation to the Board</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-kurds-and-the-syria-crisis-from-the-equation-to-the-board/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 19:53:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-kurds-and-the-syria-crisis-from-the-equation-to-the-board/</guid>
      <description>Much water has flowed since the return of Kurdish Democratic Union leader Saleh Muslim Mohammad to the northern Syrian city of Qamishli in April 2011, coming from the PKK strongholds in the Qandil mountains of northern Iraq.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert: Washington does not want to face NATO ally &#34;Turkey&#34;</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/expert-washington-does-not-want-to-face-nato-ally-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 13:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/expert-washington-does-not-want-to-face-nato-ally-turkey/</guid>
      <description>Political analyst and adviser Ali Hussein Bakir, the US administration concluded that it would be &amp;ldquo;absurd&amp;rdquo; to engage in a confrontation with Turkey after President Donald Trump confirmed his commitment to withdraw troops from Syria.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
