<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Donald Trump on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/donald-trump/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Donald Trump on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2020 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 14:37:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/donald-trump/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Trump In India And What He&#39;s Doing That The MSM Isn&#39;t Telling You</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-in-india-and-what-hes-doing-that-the-msm-isnt-telling-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 14:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-in-india-and-what-hes-doing-that-the-msm-isnt-telling-you/</guid>
      <description>Namaste, that actually means hi in Indiana, don’t worry I’m not turning a full hippie-dippie, but anyway, Donald Trump officially retweeted upon the announcement of his visit to India which we will be breaking down the significance of geopolitically, especially with all the incredible news happening around American foreign policy including the latest information about the Afghanistan Taliban peace deal that you’re not hearing about in the mainstream media, the extremely messy situation unfolding right now in Syria with Turkey Russia and China is very involved in what looks like a situation that will soon escalate to very dangerous proportions, and then, of course, we’re also gonna be talking about China Philippines there is, of course, a lot more all specifically surrounding American hegemony foreign policy, geopolitical updates that of course, you won’t hear from MSM, so I mean you don’t even hear about the topic of foreign policy being discussed in the presidential debates but it is a key important factor since American foreign policy is essentially policy of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump cuts down on IL&#39;s controversial former governor</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-cuts-down-on-ils-controversial-former-governor/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2020 20:36:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-cuts-down-on-ils-controversial-former-governor/</guid>
      <description>Rod Blagojevich was serving a 14-year sentence for multiple federal corruption convictions.
President Trump commuted Tuesday the sentence of former Illinois Governor Rod Blagojevich.
Until Tuesday, Blagojevich served a 14-year sentence for multiple federal corruption convictions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Confusion in Iowa, Bernie Sanders claims to be leading</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/confusion-in-iowa-bernie-sanders-claims-to-be-leading/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Feb 2020 19:26:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/confusion-in-iowa-bernie-sanders-claims-to-be-leading/</guid>
      <description>The results of the first primaries of the Democratic Party are slow to be official. The organizers mentioned &amp;ldquo;inconsistencies&amp;rdquo; in their collection of results.
It is launch in pain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US Ambassador: Trump ordered me to work with his lawyer Giuliani</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/us-ambassador-trump-ordered-me-to-work-with-his-lawyer-giuliani/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 16:00:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/us-ambassador-trump-ordered-me-to-work-with-his-lawyer-giuliani/</guid>
      <description>President Donald Trump has ordered him to work with his lawyer Rudy Giuliani on the Ukraine issue, and Giuliani wanted to urge Ukrainian President Volodymyr Zelensky to investigate Trump&amp;rsquo;s political rivals, US Ambassador to the European Union Gordon Sundland admitted during his House testimony on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Investigations Trump trial key witness testifies today in Congress</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/investigations-trump-trial-key-witness-testifies-today-in-congress/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2019 15:01:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/investigations-trump-trial-key-witness-testifies-today-in-congress/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (Reuters) &amp;ndash; The US House of Representatives will continue to hear public witnesses as part of the Democratic Party&amp;rsquo;s bid to try President Donald Trump on Wednesday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US &#34;House of Representatives&#34; resumes investigation to hold Trump accountable</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/us-house-of-representatives-resumes-investigation-to-hold-trump-accountable/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 18:45:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/us-house-of-representatives-resumes-investigation-to-hold-trump-accountable/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (Reuters) &amp;ndash; The US House of Representatives will resume its inquiry into President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s accountability by hearing the testimony of a senior State Department official, a day after a US judge rejected a Republican objection to the Democratic-controlled House probe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
