<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>elections on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/elections/</link>
    <description>Recent content in elections on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2024 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 06:48:42 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/elections/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Modi, Striking a Modest Tone, Is Sworn In for a Third Term</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-10-modi-striking-a-modest-tone-is-sworn-in-for-a-third-term/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 06:48:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-10-modi-striking-a-modest-tone-is-sworn-in-for-a-third-term/</guid>
      <description>Prime Minister Narendra Modi was sworn in for a third term on Thursday, promising to work for the “poor, the downtrodden and the marginalized” as he took the oath of office in a ceremony that was scaled back because of the coronavirus pandemic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flemish Nationalists Thwart Ascent of Secessionist Party in Belgian Elections</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-10-flemish-nationalists-thwart-ascent-of-secessionist-party-in-belgian-elections/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 06:08:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-10-flemish-nationalists-thwart-ascent-of-secessionist-party-in-belgian-elections/</guid>
      <description>By J. D. Longstreet
The Flemish Nationalists, in Belgium, have thwarted the ascent of a secessionist party in the Belgian elections.
The Flemish Nationalists, who are the largest party in the Flemish region of Belgium, have been able to keep the secessionist party, the New Flemish Alliance (N-VA), from gaining a majority in the Flemish parliament.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mexico’s Leftists Won Big. Investors Are Worried.</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-10-mexicos-leftists-won-big.-investors-are-worried./</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:28:08 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-10-mexicos-leftists-won-big.-investors-are-worried./</guid>
      <description>By JULIE HIRSCHFELD DAVIS and ALEXANDER BURNS
MEXICO CITY — The leftist Andres Manuel Lopez Obrador won Mexico’s presidential election on Sunday, a victory that could upend the country’s economic policies and shift its foreign relations, particularly with the United States.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Battered by Far Right in E.U. Vote, Macron Calls for New Elections in France</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-10-battered-by-far-right-in-e.u.-vote-macron-calls-for-new-elections-in-france/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 05:07:59 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-10-battered-by-far-right-in-e.u.-vote-macron-calls-for-new-elections-in-france/</guid>
      <description>PARIS — President Emmanuel Macron of France called on Saturday for new parliamentary elections to be held in June, after his party suffered a crushing defeat in the European Parliament elections, with the far right making significant gains.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In E.U. Elections, the Center Holds, but the Far Right Still Wreaks Havoc</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-10-in-e.u.-elections-the-center-holds-but-the-far-right-still-wreaks-havoc/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jun 2024 04:47:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-10-in-e.u.-elections-the-center-holds-but-the-far-right-still-wreaks-havoc/</guid>
      <description>The European Union’s parliamentary elections, held last week, were a test of the bloc’s resilience in the face of populist and nationalist movements. The results, while not a complete repudiation of the far right, were a clear rejection of the most extreme voices.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The E.U. Is Voting. It’s Never Mattered More.</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-07-the-e.u.-is-voting.-its-never-mattered-more./</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jun 2024 18:02:25 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-07-the-e.u.-is-voting.-its-never-mattered-more./</guid>
      <description>The European Union is holding its first-ever direct elections for the European Parliament. The results will determine the direction of the 27-nation bloc for the next five years.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>In Global Elections, Strongmen Are Taken Down a Notch</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-06-in-global-elections-strongmen-are-taken-down-a-notch/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jun 2024 13:37:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-06-in-global-elections-strongmen-are-taken-down-a-notch/</guid>
      <description>The world is witnessing a wave of elections in which strongmen are being challenged, and in some cases, defeated.
In the United States, President Donald Trump, who has been accused of authoritarian tendencies, is facing a tough re-election battle against former Vice President Joe Biden.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet the One Man Everyone Trusts on U.K. Election Nights</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-05-meet-the-one-man-everyone-trusts-on-u.k.-election-nights/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 11:35:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-05-meet-the-one-man-everyone-trusts-on-u.k.-election-nights/</guid>
      <description>The BBC’s Andrew Neil is a fixture of British politics, and he’s not afraid to ask the tough questions.
By Alexandra Schwartz
The BBC’s Andrew Neil is a fixture of British politics, and he’s not afraid to ask the tough questions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Needing Help to Stay in Power, Modi Loses His Aura of Invincibility</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-05-needing-help-to-stay-in-power-modi-loses-his-aura-of-invincibility/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 11:14:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-05-needing-help-to-stay-in-power-modi-loses-his-aura-of-invincibility/</guid>
      <description>By Rakesh Raman
Indian Prime Minister Narendra Modi, who was once considered invincible, is now struggling to stay in power.
Modi, who is known for his aggressive and autocratic style of governance, is facing a tough challenge from the opposition parties in the Indian state of Uttar Pradesh (UP) where he is trying to win the assembly elections to be held in February 2017.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Rival U.K. Political Leaders Clash in Bad-Tempered Election Debate</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-05-rival-u.k.-political-leaders-clash-in-bad-tempered-election-debate/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 10:54:28 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-05-rival-u.k.-political-leaders-clash-in-bad-tempered-election-debate/</guid>
      <description>LONDON—Britain’s two main political leaders clashed in a bad-tempered debate Thursday, with Prime Minister Boris Johnson accusing his Labour Party rival Jeremy Corbyn of being a Marxist who would wreck the economy and the opposition leader saying the Conservative leader was a liar.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Modi Struggles to Stay on Top&gt; 4 Takeaways From India’s Election</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-05-modi-struggles-to-stay-on-top-4-takeaways-from-indias-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jun 2024 10:13:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-05-modi-struggles-to-stay-on-top-4-takeaways-from-indias-election/</guid>
      <description>India’s ruling Bharatiya Janata Party (BJP) is struggling to maintain its majority in the country’s parliament, according to exit polls released Sunday. The polls suggest that the BJP will win between 151 and 206 seats in the 543-seat Lok Sabha, the lower house of India’s parliament, falling short of the 272 seats needed for a majority.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Surging Hard Right in Europe Stumbles Over Its Own Divisions</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-04-a-surging-hard-right-in-europe-stumbles-over-its-own-divisions/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 08:11:38 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-04-a-surging-hard-right-in-europe-stumbles-over-its-own-divisions/</guid>
      <description>The European Union is facing a crisis of legitimacy, with the rise of populist, nationalist parties that are challenging the very foundations of the bloc. These parties, which have gained significant ground in recent years, are united by their opposition to immigration, their skepticism of globalization, and their rejection of the EU’s institutions and values.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Claudia Sheinbaum Makes History as First Woman Elected to Lead Mexico</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-04-claudia-sheinbaum-makes-history-as-first-woman-elected-to-lead-mexico/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:51:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-04-claudia-sheinbaum-makes-history-as-first-woman-elected-to-lead-mexico/</guid>
      <description>City
Claudia Sheinbaum, a 56-year-old engineer and former head of the city’s environmental department, won the election for mayor of Mexico City on Sunday, making her the first woman to lead the capital in its 230-year history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Another Milestone in Mexico&gt; Its First Jewish President</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-04-another-milestone-in-mexico-its-first-jewish-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:30:44 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-04-another-milestone-in-mexico-its-first-jewish-president/</guid>
      <description>By: Yair Rosenberg
On July 1, 2018, Andrés Manuel López Obrador, a left-wing populist, was sworn in as the president of Mexico. He is the first Jewish president in the country’s history.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What to Know About Claudia Sheinbaum, Mexico’s Newly Elected President</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-04-what-to-know-about-claudia-sheinbaum-mexicos-newly-elected-president/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 07:10:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-04-what-to-know-about-claudia-sheinbaum-mexicos-newly-elected-president/</guid>
      <description>Claudia Sheinbaum, a 56-year-old engineer and former cabinet member, has been elected as Mexico’s new president. She is the first woman to hold the position and is expected to take office on December 1.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Jacob Zuma Gets His Revenge on South African Party That Shunned Him</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-04-jacob-zuma-gets-his-revenge-on-south-african-party-that-shunned-him/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 06:29:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-04-jacob-zuma-gets-his-revenge-on-south-african-party-that-shunned-him/</guid>
      <description>Jacob Zuma, the former president of South Africa, has been a polarizing figure since he took office in 2009. His tenure was marked by allegations of corruption, economic mismanagement, and a disregard for the rule of law.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brexit Champion Says He’ll Run for Parliament, Jolting U.K. Election</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-04-brexit-champion-says-hell-run-for-parliament-jolting-u.k.-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jun 2024 05:49:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-04-brexit-champion-says-hell-run-for-parliament-jolting-u.k.-election/</guid>
      <description>Boris Johnson, the former foreign secretary who has been a leading advocate for Britain leaving the European Union, said on Monday that he would run for Parliament in a by-election in a northern English constituency, a move that could complicate the political landscape in the country.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Small Army Combating a Flood of Deepfakes in India’s Election</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-01-a-small-army-combating-a-flood-of-deepfakes-in-indias-election/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jun 2024 05:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-06-01-a-small-army-combating-a-flood-of-deepfakes-in-indias-election/</guid>
      <description>The Indian government has deployed a small army of fact-checkers to combat a flood of deepfakes during the country’s general election, which began on Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Historic breakthrough of Sinn Fein in the legislative elections in Ireland</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/historic-breakthrough-of-sinn-fein-in-the-legislative-elections-in-ireland/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Feb 2020 14:21:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/historic-breakthrough-of-sinn-fein-in-the-legislative-elections-in-ireland/</guid>
      <description>Prime Minister Leo Varadkar’s party, Fine Gael, was the big loser in this Sunday, February 9, election. He comes third.
A setback for the party of Prime Minister Leo Varadkar, the Fine Gael, which comes in the third position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Israel on the way to new elections in March</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-on-the-way-to-new-elections-in-march/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Dec 2019 13:19:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/israel-on-the-way-to-new-elections-in-march/</guid>
      <description>Israelis will go to the polls for the third time in a year. Polls again give Netanyahu and his rival Gantz neck and neck.
The Israeli political class was preparing the ground Wednesday evening for new elections, at the beginning of March, the third in less than a year, with the flavor of a new duel between Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu, now charged with corruption, and his rival Benny Gantz.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Algerian interior minister calls election opponents &#34;traitors and gays&#34;</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/algerian-interior-minister-calls-election-opponents-traitors-and-gays/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 14:12:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/algerian-interior-minister-calls-election-opponents-traitors-and-gays/</guid>
      <description>Algerian Interior Minister Salaheddine Dahmoun provoked controversy after he violently attacked opponents of the December 12 presidential election, calling them &amp;ldquo;traitors, mercenaries, homosexuals and the remains of colonialism.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
