<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Trump on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/trump/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Trump on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2020 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:34:34 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/trump/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Musk accuses Biden of lying about the immigration crisis</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-03-03-musk-accuses-biden-of-lying-about-the-immigration-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Mar 2024 19:34:34 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/posts/2024-03-03-musk-accuses-biden-of-lying-about-the-immigration-crisis/</guid>
      <description>The billionaire and American businessman, Elon Musk, accused the American president on Sunday of lying about the immigration crisis, stating that President Joe Biden&amp;rsquo;s remarks about wanting to solve the issue of illegal immigration are &amp;ldquo;pure lies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump chances of winning the election are diminishing</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/Trump%20chances%20of%20winning%20the%20election%20are%20diminishing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Oct 2020 09:37:58 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/Trump%20chances%20of%20winning%20the%20election%20are%20diminishing/</guid>
      <description>The American newspaper &amp;ldquo;The Hill&amp;rdquo; published on its website an article by writer Niall Stanig in which he affirmed that President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s chances of winning a second term are diminishing, while opinion polls indicate that his Democratic opponent, Joe Biden, has advanced by a large margin that is difficult for him to overcome.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump vs Fauci: President and doctor spar over unproven drug</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-vs-fauci-president-and-doctor-spar-over-unproven-drug/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Mar 2020 00:16:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-vs-fauci-president-and-doctor-spar-over-unproven-drug/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;mdash; In an extraordinary exchange, President Donald Trump and the government&amp;rsquo;s top infectious disease expert, Dr. Anthony Fauci, publicly sparred Friday on whether a malaria drug would work to treat people with coronavirus disease.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump dubs COVID-19 ‘Chinese virus&#39; despite hate crime risks</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-dubs-covid-19-chinese-virus-despite-hate-crime-risks/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 23:16:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-dubs-covid-19-chinese-virus-despite-hate-crime-risks/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;mdash; President Donald Trump said Wednesday that he doesn&amp;rsquo;t think calling COVID-19 the &amp;ldquo;Chinese virus&amp;rdquo; &amp;mdash; or the &amp;ldquo;kung-flu,&amp;rdquo; as one administration official reportedly called it &amp;mdash; puts Asian Americans at risk of retaliation despite growing reports they are facing virus-related discrimination.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s latest travel ban highlights gaps in containment net</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trumps-latest-travel-ban-highlights-gaps-in-containment-net/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 15:20:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trumps-latest-travel-ban-highlights-gaps-in-containment-net/</guid>
      <description>NEW YORK (AP) &amp;mdash; In the weeks before President Donald Trump spoke from the Oval Office to announce restrictions on travelers from more than two dozen countries in Europe, thousands of people from the region already had stepped off planes at U.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump economic team grasps for credibility with outbreak</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-economic-team-grasps-for-credibility-with-outbreak/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 21:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-economic-team-grasps-for-credibility-with-outbreak/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;mdash; During the financial crisis a decade ago, President Barack Obama could look around the room and turn to an economist who served as Harvard&amp;rsquo;s president, a former president of the New York Federal Reserve and a renowned academic considered one of the world&amp;rsquo;s authorities on the Great Depression.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>It looks like Trump is trying to trick people into filling out &#34;census&#34; forms online</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/it-looks-like-trump-is-trying-to-trick-people-into-filling-out-census-forms-online/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Mar 2020 12:26:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/it-looks-like-trump-is-trying-to-trick-people-into-filling-out-census-forms-online/</guid>
      <description>Shortly ahead of the US National 2020 census, President Trump&amp;rsquo;s campaign is running ads on Facebook that some are saying are misleading users into thinking that a data-gathering and fundraising survey for the Trump presidential campaign is actually the official US national census.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump names Rep. Mark Meadows his new chief of staff</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-names-rep-mark-meadows-his-new-chief-of-staff/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Mar 2020 02:16:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-names-rep-mark-meadows-his-new-chief-of-staff/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;mdash; Under fire for his handling of the coronavirus crisis, President Donald Trump on Friday announced a major staff overhaul, naming Rep. Mark Meadows as his new chief of staff and replacing Mick Mulvaney, who has been acting in the role for more than a year.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump seeks high court approval to speed deportations</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-seeks-high-court-approval-to-speed-deportations/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Mar 2020 00:30:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-seeks-high-court-approval-to-speed-deportations/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;mdash; The particular person slipped into the U.S.from Tijuana, Mexico, and made it upright 25 yards from the border earlier than he was arrested.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump urges tranquil even as US reports worrisome recent virus case</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-urges-tranquil-even-as-us-reports-worrisome-recent-virus-case/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 06:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-urges-tranquil-even-as-us-reports-worrisome-recent-virus-case/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;mdash; President Donald Trump declared Wednesday that a widespread U.S. outbreak of the recent respiratory virus sweeping the globe isn&amp;rsquo;t inevitable even as high well being authorities at his aspect warned Americans that more infections are coming.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump campaign sues NY Events for defamation over Putin</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-campaign-sues-ny-events-for-defamation-over-putin/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 01:19:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-campaign-sues-ny-events-for-defamation-over-putin/</guid>
      <description>NEW YORK (AP) &amp;mdash; The campaign to reelect President Donald Trump sued The Unique York Events for defamation Wednesday, announcing it was accountable for an essay by a extinct executive editor for the newspaper that claimed the campaign made a cope with Russian officials to defeat Hillary Clinton in 2016.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump faces credibility test as he performs down virus threat</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-faces-credibility-test-as-he-performs-down-virus-threat/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 23:24:12 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-faces-credibility-test-as-he-performs-down-virus-threat/</guid>
      <description>WASHINGTON (AP) &amp;mdash; President Donald Trump faces a well-known challenge in grappling with the brand new coronavirus outbreak: Asking Americans to trust him after he and high advisers maintain contradicted federal scientists in playing down the threat.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>when Trump recounts the strike against General Soleimani</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/when-trump-recounts-the-strike-against-general-soleimani/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2020 20:09:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/when-trump-recounts-the-strike-against-general-soleimani/</guid>
      <description>In a meeting with donors to the Republican Party, the White House tenant recounted on Friday the final moments of the Iranian general, killed on January 3 by an American strike.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Donald Trump mocked by Trudeau&#39;s mockery alongside Macron and Johnson</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/donald-trump-mocked-by-trudeaus-mockery-alongside-macron-and-johnson/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 Dec 2019 17:18:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/donald-trump-mocked-by-trudeaus-mockery-alongside-macron-and-johnson/</guid>
      <description>The US president did not appreciate the words of his Canadian counterpart in an informal conversation, captured Tuesday evening by Anglo-Saxon media.
The tone was informal, the faces relaxed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US House Intelligence Committee approves Trump&#39;s impeachment</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/us-house-intelligence-committee-approves-trumps-impeachment/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Dec 2019 14:52:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/us-house-intelligence-committee-approves-trumps-impeachment/</guid>
      <description>Washington &amp;ndash; The US House of Representatives Intelligence Committee on Tuesday approved a report dismissing US President Donald Trump, the Bloomberg News Agency reported.
The Committee adopted the report by 13 votes to 9.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Foreign Policy and NATO Why does Trump adopt the principle of &#34;America first&#34;?</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/foreign-policy-and-nato-why-does-trump-adopt-the-principle-of-america-first/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2019 16:20:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/foreign-policy-and-nato-why-does-trump-adopt-the-principle-of-america-first/</guid>
      <description>US President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s participation in the NATO summit in London, marking the 70th anniversary of the alliance, raises questions about Trump&amp;rsquo;s vision of foreign policy issues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Times: Changing Alliances Feed Syria War</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/times-changing-alliances-feed-syria-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 13:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/times-changing-alliances-feed-syria-war/</guid>
      <description>An analysis by the Middle East Times correspondent Richard Spinner says the changing alliances that fuel the war that has ravaged Syria for years are endless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>&#34;Scandal of Ukraine&#34; .. Suspicions about the complicity of Pompeo and Pines</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/suspicions-about-the-complicity-of-pompeo-and-pines/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2019 10:59:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/suspicions-about-the-complicity-of-pompeo-and-pines/</guid>
      <description>As public hearings into the investigation into the ouster of US President Donald Trump enter their second week, there is suspicion of complicity over US Vice President Mike Pence and Secretary of State Mike Pompeo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Beijing&#39;s weapons in battle and Why America waged a trade war on China</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/beijings-weapons-in-battle-and-why-america-waged-a-trade-war-on-china/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 26 Oct 2019 20:41:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/beijings-weapons-in-battle-and-why-america-waged-a-trade-war-on-china/</guid>
      <description>In the aftermath of the Cold War, the United States changed its policy and priorities and viewed China&amp;rsquo;s economic emergence as a major threat to its interests in the decades to come.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s policy in Syria could reorganize the state</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trumps-policy-in-syria-could-reorganize-the-state/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 12:16:07 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trumps-policy-in-syria-could-reorganize-the-state/</guid>
      <description>US President Donald Trump&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;reactionary&amp;rdquo; foreign policy would bring the Islamic State back to Syria, writer Kim Seggupta says.
One of the hallmarks of Trump&amp;rsquo;s foreign policy is his lack of success against adversaries and his failure to stand by allies, the writer adds in an article in The Independent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump trial: Democrats take new measures, half Americans support president impeachment</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-trial-democrats-take-new-measures-half-americans-support-president-impeachment/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Oct 2019 11:44:24 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-trial-democrats-take-new-measures-half-americans-support-president-impeachment/</guid>
      <description>Ten Democrats, led by Foreign Relations Committee member Bob Menendez, have called on Secretary of State Mike Pompeo to explain the reasons and motives behind the dismissal of former US ambassador to Ukraine Mary Jovanovich on the backdrop of pressures exerted by both Trump&amp;rsquo;s lawyers and his son to dismiss her because of her consistent position Detective later.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What makes Trump obedient to Erdogan?</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-makes-trump-obedient-to-erdogan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 16:35:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/what-makes-trump-obedient-to-erdogan/</guid>
      <description>Turkish President Recep Tayyip Erdogan often finds a listening ear from US President Donald Trump and the relationship is unusual, during which the Turkish president is used to persuading Trump to take positions that put him at odds with his national security aides and his Republican allies, The New York Times said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The White House Refuses to Cooperate with Investigations The move would put the United States in a constitutional crisis</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-white-house-refuses-to-cooperate-with-investigations-the-move-would-put-the-united-states-in-a-constitutional-crisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Oct 2019 11:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/the-white-house-refuses-to-cooperate-with-investigations-the-move-would-put-the-united-states-in-a-constitutional-crisis/</guid>
      <description>The White House has decided to refuse to cooperate with ongoing investigations that Democrats are seeking to begin proceedings to isolate President Donald Trump, arguing that the investigation lacks &amp;ldquo;constitutional legitimacy&amp;rdquo; and would put the United States in a constitutional crisis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Expert: Washington does not want to face NATO ally &#34;Turkey&#34;</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/expert-washington-does-not-want-to-face-nato-ally-turkey/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Oct 2019 13:14:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/expert-washington-does-not-want-to-face-nato-ally-turkey/</guid>
      <description>Political analyst and adviser Ali Hussein Bakir, the US administration concluded that it would be &amp;ldquo;absurd&amp;rdquo; to engage in a confrontation with Turkey after President Donald Trump confirmed his commitment to withdraw troops from Syria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump news conference with president of Finland</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-news-conference/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Oct 2019 18:47:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-news-conference/</guid>
      <description>Look at all the press that you attract you believe that&amp;rsquo;s very impressive enough talk to me. I hope not you lucky. Thank you very much today.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
