<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Things on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/things/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Things on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2020 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 13:18:18 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/things/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>10 Things to Know for Today</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/10-things-to-know-for-today-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 13:18:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/10-things-to-know-for-today-2/</guid>
      <description>Your daily look at late-breaking news, upcoming events and the stories that will be talked about today:
  XI VISITS VIRUS&#39; EPICENTER AS RECESSION FEARS GRIP WORLD China&amp;rsquo;s president visits Wuhan, the center of the global virus outbreak, as Italy begins a nationwide travel ban and people worldwide brace for the possibility of recession.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Things to Know for Today</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/10-things-to-know-for-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 04 Mar 2020 14:20:55 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/10-things-to-know-for-today/</guid>
      <description>Your day-to-day admire at late-breaking news, upcoming events and the experiences that can be talked about this present day:
  BIDEN HAS MOST WINS, SANDERS BIGGEST PRIZE A resurgent Joe Biden ratings nine victories across the country &amp;mdash; including Texas &amp;mdash; whereas progressive rival Bernie Sanders seizes Clear Tuesday&amp;rsquo;s perfect prize with a snatch in California.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>10 Things to Know about the current time</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/10-things-to-know-for-on-the-current-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 12:22:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/10-things-to-know-for-on-the-current-time/</guid>
      <description>Your day-to-day sight at uninteresting-breaking files, upcoming events and the tales that will most definitely be talked about on the current time:
  CORONAVIRUS CASES CONTINUE TO SPIKE IN ASIA Because the worst-hit areas in China and South Korea continue to strive against with the viral epidemic, worries about infection and containment unfold across the globe.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
