<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>russia on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/russia/</link>
    <description>Recent content in russia on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2020 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 14:37:39 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/russia/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Trump In India And What He&#39;s Doing That The MSM Isn&#39;t Telling You</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-in-india-and-what-hes-doing-that-the-msm-isnt-telling-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2020 14:37:39 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/trump-in-india-and-what-hes-doing-that-the-msm-isnt-telling-you/</guid>
      <description>Namaste, that actually means hi in Indiana, don’t worry I’m not turning a full hippie-dippie, but anyway, Donald Trump officially retweeted upon the announcement of his visit to India which we will be breaking down the significance of geopolitically, especially with all the incredible news happening around American foreign policy including the latest information about the Afghanistan Taliban peace deal that you’re not hearing about in the mainstream media, the extremely messy situation unfolding right now in Syria with Turkey Russia and China is very involved in what looks like a situation that will soon escalate to very dangerous proportions, and then, of course, we’re also gonna be talking about China Philippines there is, of course, a lot more all specifically surrounding American hegemony foreign policy, geopolitical updates that of course, you won’t hear from MSM, so I mean you don’t even hear about the topic of foreign policy being discussed in the presidential debates but it is a key important factor since American foreign policy is essentially policy of the world.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>US conduct exercises in case of nuclear war with Russia</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/us-conduct-exercises-in-case-of-nuclear-war-with-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Feb 2020 00:59:21 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/us-conduct-exercises-in-case-of-nuclear-war-with-russia/</guid>
      <description>The United States conducted &amp;ldquo;small&amp;rdquo; exercises in the event of a Russian nuclear strike against Europe and a retaliatory attack by the United States, a Pentagon spokesman said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bernie Sanders: &#34;Here is the message to Russia: Stay out of American elections.</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/bernie-sanders-here-is-the-message-to-russia/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 22:58:51 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/bernie-sanders-here-is-the-message-to-russia/</guid>
      <description>‘Sen. Bernie Sanders answer to the reporter asking about the claim that Russia is helping get Bernie elected. ​” He is telling us they are interfering in this campaign right now in 2020.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Times: Changing Alliances Feed Syria War</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/times-changing-alliances-feed-syria-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 29 Nov 2019 13:07:36 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/times-changing-alliances-feed-syria-war/</guid>
      <description>An analysis by the Middle East Times correspondent Richard Spinner says the changing alliances that fuel the war that has ravaged Syria for years are endless.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Oil contracts in euros Russia continues to get rid of the dominance of the dollar</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/oil-contracts-in-euros-russia-continues-to-get-rid-of-the-dominance-of-the-dollar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 21:10:29 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/oil-contracts-in-euros-russia-continues-to-get-rid-of-the-dominance-of-the-dollar/</guid>
      <description>Russia&amp;rsquo;s biggest oil company, Igor Sechin, has shifted completely to using the euro in its contracts instead of the dollar, a move aimed at protecting its dealings from US sanctions, Rosneft&amp;rsquo;s chief executive said.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia sends 300 additional troops to the Syrian-Turkish border</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/russia-sends-300-additional-troops-to-the-syrian-turkish-border/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Oct 2019 21:00:18 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/russia-sends-300-additional-troops-to-the-syrian-turkish-border/</guid>
      <description>The Russian Defense Ministry announced the arrival of about 300 Russian military police to Syria to help the withdrawal of Kurdish forces from the border with Turkey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Russia warns and Kurds mobilize .. List of the latest developments of the Turkish operation in Syria</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/russia-warns-and-kurds-mobilize-list-of-the-latest-developments-of-the-turkish-operation-in-syria/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Oct 2019 12:31:05 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/russia-warns-and-kurds-mobilize-list-of-the-latest-developments-of-the-turkish-operation-in-syria/</guid>
      <description>Turkish troops are preparing to launch a military operation in northern Syria with the aim of keeping Kurdish fighters out of their borders and establishing a safe area, enabling Syrian refugees to return home.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Little Girl Gets Scolded By An Abusive Teacher, Only To Kick Him In The Crotch</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/little-girl-gets-scolded-by-an-abusive-teacher-only-to-kick-him-in-the-crotch/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jun 2019 21:22:54 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/little-girl-gets-scolded-by-an-abusive-teacher-only-to-kick-him-in-the-crotch/</guid>
      <description>This aggressive teacher in Russia will probably think twice before humiliating another kid in his class again. He was rightfully put in his place after one little girl kicked him in the groin for his abusive behavior.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
