<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Coronavirus on PepsFeeder</title>
    <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/coronavirus/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Coronavirus on PepsFeeder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; Copyright 2020 pepsfeeder</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:30:15 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://pepsfeeder.github.io/tags/coronavirus/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>DIY -- 24 method how to make your own hand sanitizer</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/diy-24-method-how-to-make-your-own-hand-sanitizer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2020 00:30:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/diy-24-method-how-to-make-your-own-hand-sanitizer/</guid>
      <description>Liquid hand sanitizers-mostly alcohol-based gels-have experienced an explosion in popularity over the last 10 years. If you’ve recently traveled by plane or set foot in a classroom in the US, chances are you’ve seen hand sanitizers in use.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus pandemic leads Amazon to ban many non-essential items</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-pandemic-leads-amazon-to-ban-many-non-essential-items/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Mar 2020 09:18:45 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-pandemic-leads-amazon-to-ban-many-non-essential-items/</guid>
      <description>Faced with merchandise shortages in the United States and Europe due to the Covid-19 coronavirus pandemic, Amazon has instituted sweeping changes on which products it will store and ship from its warehouses over the next three weeks, in a move it said was aimed at keeping essential items in stock and speeding up orders.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus news is dominating readers&#39; attention</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-news-is-dominating-readers-attention/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 20:17:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-news-is-dominating-readers-attention/</guid>
      <description>If you feel like you&amp;rsquo;ve been glued to the news lately, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. We&amp;rsquo;re collectively reading much more news during the novel coronavirus pandemic than normal, according to new publisher traffic data.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus means The Hunt and Trolls get early streaming rental options</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-means-the-hunt-and-trolls-get-early-streaming-rental-options/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Mar 2020 00:16:41 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-means-the-hunt-and-trolls-get-early-streaming-rental-options/</guid>
      <description>You can&amp;rsquo;t go to the movies. So some movies are going to come to you.
That&amp;rsquo;s the message from media giant NBCUniversal, whose movie studio is going to start letting customers rent a selection of movies that are supposed to be in theaters now.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How coronavirus is affecting the restaurant business, in one chart</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/how-coronavirus-is-affecting-the-restaurant-business-in-one-chart/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 17:24:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/how-coronavirus-is-affecting-the-restaurant-business-in-one-chart/</guid>
      <description>In addition to its severe cost to human life, the novel coronavirus has wreaked havoc on a number of industries including airlines, cruises, and conferences. As people and governments and public health experts stress the importance of social distancing as a way to stem the spread of the contagion, restaurants are seeing major declines in patronage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google&#39;s coronavirus website isn&#39;t what Trump described</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/googles-coronavirus-website-isnt-what-trump-described/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Mar 2020 11:18:53 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/googles-coronavirus-website-isnt-what-trump-described/</guid>
      <description>Two days after President Donald Trump announced that Google was racing to build a site to help Americans find coronavirus testing, people are still confused about what&amp;rsquo;s actually going on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus prompts Microsoft, Google, and Zoom to offer free software</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-prompts-microsoft-google-and-zoom-to-offer-free-software/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Mar 2020 20:18:57 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-prompts-microsoft-google-and-zoom-to-offer-free-software/</guid>
      <description>As the number of infections and deaths from the novel coronavirus rise drastically, governments, schools, and companies around the world are instituting more drastic measures to rein in the virus&amp;rsquo;s spread.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus is creating new businesses, from robots to anti-spitting hats</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-is-creating-new-businesses-from-robots-to-anti-spitting-hats/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Mar 2020 02:18:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-is-creating-new-businesses-from-robots-to-anti-spitting-hats/</guid>
      <description>The outbreak of the novel coronavirus is crashing global markets and affecting everything from air travel to the film industry to local businesses. Still, some companies stand to benefit somehow from this outbreak, which has now spread to scores of countries and infected more than 100,000 people.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Flu and coronavirus: Similar symptoms, different fears</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/flu-and-coronavirus-similar-symptoms-different-fears/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 22:22:27 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/flu-and-coronavirus-similar-symptoms-different-fears/</guid>
      <description>Is it the flu, a cold or the new coronavirus? Patients and doctors alike are parsing signs of illness to figure out who needs what tests or care and how worried they should be.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus phishing attacks and email scams are on the rise</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-phishing-attacks-and-email-scams-are-on-the-rise/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2020 03:28:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-phishing-attacks-and-email-scams-are-on-the-rise/</guid>
      <description>If you didn&amp;rsquo;t have enough to worry about with the new coronavirus, here&amp;rsquo;s one more thing: Scammers are using the outbreak to steal your information through phishing attempts or to lure you into downloading a different kind of virus.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus price gougers can&#39;t be stopped by Amazon</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-price-gougers-cant-be-stopped-by-amazon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Mar 2020 02:23:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-price-gougers-cant-be-stopped-by-amazon/</guid>
      <description>If you searched for hand sanitizer on Amazon on Thursday, one of the first listings that greeted you was a two-pack of Purell in 1-liter bottles selling for $350.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus outbreak: How Facebook, Twitter, YouTube, and TikTok are dealing with hoaxes</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-outbreak-how-facebook-twitter-youtube-and-tiktok-are-dealing-with-hoaxes/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 14:27:26 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-outbreak-how-facebook-twitter-youtube-and-tiktok-are-dealing-with-hoaxes/</guid>
      <description>Social media companies are increasing their vigilance about removing coronavirus conspiracies. Facebook, in particular, continues to update its policies as the outbreak &amp;mdash; and corresponding disinformation &amp;mdash; spreads.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus cancellations of tech industry events cost $500 million at least</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-cancellations-of-tech-industry-events-cost-500-million-at-least/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Mar 2020 02:16:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-cancellations-of-tech-industry-events-cost-500-million-at-least/</guid>
      <description>As the novel coronavirus continues to take a human and economic toll across the world, the lucrative business of tech conferences is not immune.
The direct economic loss from the cancellation from eight major tech conferences including Google I/O, Facebook&amp;rsquo;s F8 event, and Mobile World Congress over coronavirus has already reached $666 million, according to estimates the data intelligence company PredictHQ pulled for Recode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Amazon, coronavirus supplies are proliferating --- and selling fast</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/on-amazon-coronavirus-supplies-are-proliferating-and-selling-fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Feb 2020 13:26:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/on-amazon-coronavirus-supplies-are-proliferating-and-selling-fast/</guid>
      <description>Amazon talked about on Thursday that it blocked more than 1,000,000 gadgets from sale on its marketplace in contemporary weeks that made counterfeit claims about defending in opposition to the original coronavirus, as schemers all around the globe regarded to realize a transient buck amid a world health menace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus is the first test for AI, robots, and drones that can prevent pandemics</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-is-the-first-test-for-ai-robots-and-drones-that-can-prevent-pandemics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 03:25:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-is-the-first-test-for-ai-robots-and-drones-that-can-prevent-pandemics/</guid>
      <description>The unconventional coronavirus that first appeared in mainland China has now spread internationally, with greater than 82,000 reported conditions and nearly 3,000 deaths, as of Thursday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus is causing more people to work from home or remotely, surge in Zoom and Slack interest</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-is-causing-more-people-to-work-from-home-or-remotely-surge-in-zoom-and-slack-interest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2020 13:51:43 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-is-causing-more-people-to-work-from-home-or-remotely-surge-in-zoom-and-slack-interest/</guid>
      <description>A strain of coronavirus will also be reaching pandemic proportions, having killed 2,700 other folks and infected bigger than 81,000 other folks in bigger than 40 worldwide locations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moderna Coronavirus Vaccine Samples Shipped</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/moderna-coronavirus-vaccine-samples-shipped/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 18:21:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/moderna-coronavirus-vaccine-samples-shipped/</guid>
      <description>Moderna shipped the predominant samples of messenger RNA based coronavirus vaccine to the National Institute of Allergy and Infectious Disease in Bethesda Maryland. Human clinical trials could perhaps level-headed commence in 6 weeks and the outcomes could perhaps very neatly be accessible in July.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Coronavirus, the first Italian death: it is one of the two patients from Veneto. He was 78 years old, died in Padua</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-the-first-italian-death/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2020 23:30:35 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/coronavirus-the-first-italian-death/</guid>
      <description>The first death in Italy from the virus. The man tested positive for Coronavirus died on Friday evening shortly after 22.45. The hospital will be closed and emptied</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why is there no specific medicine against Coronavirus in the world so far?</title>
      <link>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/medicine-against-coronavirus-in-the-world-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2020 14:17:20 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pepsfeeder.github.io/medicine-against-coronavirus-in-the-world-so-far/</guid>
      <description>The severe acute respiratory syndrome (SARS) that broke out in Guangdong in February 2003 and the Middle East respiratory syndrome (MERS) that broke out in Saudi Arabia in September 2012 were caused by SARS-CoV and MERS-CoV coronaviruses, respectively.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
